Crafting.
At noon.
Is there a better feeling in the world?
Right now, the answer is no.
Dude, I feel amazing right now.
Yesterday was not that great, let's be honest, okay?
I lost a lot of stuff.
But the weird thing about Minecraft is that when I have a big loss like that, it's usually the day after, especially in the morning.
Where I'm like, god, damn, I need to play again.
I need to get back in and get it all back, you know?
But even better this time.
It's almost like a roguelite with a one-day delay.
Normally in a roguelite game, you immediately get the feeling when you die, okay, let's change up the build a bit, you know, let's do it differently.
Now it's like... personal.
Today we shall completely dominate the game.
And we're using the mouse for this.
That way we can't make any mistakes.
Also apologize to the Vought Watchers.
Or the normally stream watchers who now are forced to become part of the Vought Watcher Covenant.
I do stream at irregular schedules, I apologize.
I stream when I feel like it.
And this is one of the perks of being my own boss, so to speak, right now.
So I'm taking full advantage of that.
Now that I don't do a 9 to 5, I definitely don't want to do a 9 to 5 with games.
And that way, you are guaranteed that whenever I play a game, it's gonna be with the utmost satisfaction and enjoyableness.
So every time I do upload something, you are guaranteed that I will be having full enjoyment.
There we go.
That was a terrible speech.
Absolutely horrible.
I did my best.
Alright, let's launch the game.
I'm ready.
I'll try to get some late streams in as well, you know.
This one was quite early in the morning.
Or it is, it's not like it was.
It is still an early stream.
We're gonna try and switch it up a bit.
Sometimes I do get the urge to play late at night.
Although that's usually the time when I would put on a movie and chill with Jackie, you know.
God, this music is so good.
Oh man, I just relish my time.
In Blueprints.
Such an amazing game.
This takes me right back, you know.
Just walking along those halls.
Solving those puzzles and...
Taking it all in.
Man.
I'm not afraid to say it.
Blueprints is a masterpiece.
It is from Blueprints, yes.
This is the music from that game.
And this is just one of many absolutely fantastic tracks.
Highly recommend that game.
If you're just slightly into puzzles.
And a nice...
Or if you're a fan of a nice ambiance and atmosphere.
Then that's the game for you.
Okay, let's turn on Minecraft sounds.
Somehow I feel like the song we just had could work pretty well in Minecraft.
Imagine you're out there mining, you know.
In Minecraft.
And that song comes on?
From Blueprints.
I mean, I would dig that, man.
Maybe we should do something like that at some point.
Okay, so hold on.
Switch.
There we go.
Now with multiplayer.
I feel like that's an old message.
Very old message.
Dum dum dum.
Let's go!
Let's do it.
Alright.
So I'm making...
By the way, I looked it up.
Apparently in English this is called tank tracks.
But they can also be called caterpillar tracks.
That's what I was trying to say last time.
In Danish we say laufel.
You know?
Which means larvae feet.
But yeah.
That is what that is.
I think we're gonna go for the low-hanging fruit right now.
And actually use what we know works.
I'm gonna go into the nether with the now...
Fully functional digging machine on a track.
But before I do, we're gonna go get some iron.
Because I want more tracks.
We don't have enough.
It ain't enough, Captain.
You know, actually, hold on.
We're gonna...
Let's really fix the problems that I have in this game.
At its base.
At its core, what is the issue with my gameplay?
Let's think it's...
Let's make a list.
This one is...
Let's change this list.
We don't need this.
This is fine.
Delete it all.
They're not an easier way to delete it all.
Maybe control A?
Nope.
Damn it.
Okay, here we go.
The first one is...
I never have enough...
Food.
Number two.
I...
Am too...
Damn...
Greedy.
Know...
When to stop!
See exhibit last time.
I was in the nether.
I knew when to stop, and yet I kept going.
Like an idiot.
But...
This one would not have happened...
If I did this one.
You know?
We need...
A checklist...
Of items...
Before going on expeditions.
Just like in the olden days.
Because this...
There's a reason they have checklists for pilots when they go fly aircraft.
You know?
This is me.
Going on an expedition is like flying an aircraft.
Make sure the aircraft is fueled.
Make sure all the...
Bolts and...
Nuts are tightened.
You know?
We don't want the damn thing to fall apart in the air.
I just built some stuff on myself.
Good job Oliver.
Okay.
These are basically the root problems.
Whoops.
Now.
How do we fix them?
Uh...
Regarding number one.
I never have enough food.
We need a...
Answer.
Make...
A...
N...
Automated...
Cow...
Killing...
Machine...
And harvest the food.
This is...
Really the ultimate...
Solution.
Right?
This is like the end game.
Let's try to do that.
Right now.
We need to fix these core problems with the gameplay.
Never again shall I run out of food.
First we sort.
Everything gets sorted.
You go in there.
That one.
I have so many of those.
Nice.
Oh...
Uh...
We also have some grass.
It seems.
And the side casings.
All this...
Create stuff goes in here.
Although this one...
Uh...
Is now a working...
Thing.
Let's leave it here.
Wow.
That's full.
I would say lever is this.
Same with rails.
Can I put rails in here?
No.
No rails here either.
Well not the...
Kinda rails I'm talking about.
See this is my food situation right now.
I'm fucking...
Running on sweet berries.
Absolute disaster.
Terrible.
This cannot...
Go on like this.
And also the silk touch is breaking my heart.
I hate it.
Do we have any diamonds?
We have no diamonds.
Ah...
Okay, I guess I'll stick with the silk touch for now.
Yeah.
And...
Uh...
We should make a...
Um...
Toolbox.
Chest, cogwheel, golden sheet, and leather.
Chest.
Okay, we don't have that.
Uh...
Golden sheet.
Two of those.
Cogwheel.
Should have one of those.
Yup.
There we go.
Uh...
Now the chest just requires wood I believe.
Wonderful.
Toolbox.
Acquired.
Wonderful.
We're back to that.
Great.
Maybe I'll even make a second.
No, I'm not.
Don't be greedy now.
I keep 24 planks on me.
Uh...
Okay, let's work...
Actually, I do need this food.
We will require the shitty food for a while.
While we make the cow killing machine.
Alright, let's think about this.
So a cow killing machine...
I'm actually gonna bring this list with me.
Uh...
How do we do this?
I guess we would need a...
A bunch of cows, obviously.
Inside an enclosure.
Cows.
In enclosure.
Uh...
Find a way...
To feed them...
Automatically.
Answer.
Deployer.
Would be my guess.
Uh...
Then we need a killing method.
Let's say they're all in like a square enclosure.
We could have a floor...
That is lava.
Or maybe...
A blaster.
We could use a blaster.
Blast mechanism.
Or...
Maybe even a drill...
Mechanism.
That's my...
First thought.
Let's start with this.
Find a way to feed them automatically.
Let's experiment with the Deployer.
Go to sleep.
Okay.
There's nothing in here!
No, okay.
Deployer is in here.
No!
They're actually out here.
In fact, I have five of them, I believe.
Look at my tank.
Totally stole the design from the ponder, but...
Whatever!
It's mine.
I made it.
Did I just plant that?
Don't do that.
It's gonna hurt me in the butt later.
Literally.
No!
Did I take them back?
Why am I such a wild animal?
What compelled me to do such a thing?
Back in we go.
I mean, okay.
I tried to solve the food situation with this, right?
It's just a little slow.
Let me make them into bread, actually.
Okay.
That's a good amount of food for now.
Don't eat those right now.
Bread is good.
I mean...
But steak is better.
And boy, I had steak with Fritz yesterday and it was incredible.
It was just as good as I had hoped.
Ah, wait, wait.
I needed a deployer.
Which I have.
Somewhere.
There we go.
Now the deployer needs to be powered.
Ah, but let's use...
The engine for this.
Let's just be super...
Um...
Naughty.
And lazy.
No reason not to do that right now.
It's just proof of concept, right?
We just...
I could also hand crank it.
I guess just for testing purposes.
Uh, and the...
Oh, did I just take all the food feed?
Cow feed?
Shit.
Okay, we have a bit...
So that's okay.
So we have the enclosure already with animals.
Uh, let's try and see how this works.
Let's do the naive thing.
Okay, whatever.
You're free.
We're just gonna put it there.
Is that connected properly?
I'm not even sure if it is.
Wait, are they actually...
Are they attracted to it?
While it's holding it?
Because that would solve so many problems!
Oh my god.
I need, uh, fuel.
For Huel.
No, that's not Huel.
Huel is something else.
Let's get, uh...
Also, we have nothing planted here.
That's kind of a sadness.
I will manually grab some wheat here.
I don't care.
Oh, maybe you can't grab the ones on the edge.
Huh.
Oh, we're also missing some stuff there, I see.
Oops.
I really should disassemble this, because it's ugly.
And we can use all the parts.
No!
They all escaped!
Fucking assholes!
Give them an arm?
And they take a whole fucking...
I don't know, half of a body.
I messed up the expression.
Damn it!
What?
Oh, great.
What now?
Oh, man.
I need a fence.
We gotta make this fence twice as high at that spot.
Why didn't I think of this?
Okay, let's lure them back in.
Come on, now.
Here's foodies.
I know you want it.
Come this way.
Yes, you too.
Come on, then.
Everyone.
Wait, I have a gate.
Over here.
Hey, you want this?
Come.
Come on.
That's it.
Yeah, here we go.
Oh, come inside, come inside.
Look what I got for you.
Oh, don't bunch up too much now.
Come on.
Dumb animals.
No, no, sorry.
Here.
I didn't mean it.
Come on.
Guys, come on.
Follow me.
There we go.
Now.
We need fuel.
That's why I did this.
Okay.
This may actually not be enough, by the way.
They may be able to escape still.
Let's do that instead.
There's no way they can get out now.
I refuse to believe it.
Okay, now with that...
We need to...
I'm hearing a skeleton?
Oh, it's gotta be below the house.
Maybe I don't have enough light there.
And I'm blanking right now.
What did I do?
I needed to...
Oh, fuel.
Right.
Fuel.
Don't have a lot of that.
Oh, nice.
Okay, that's good.
My question is, like, let's say I put 30 coal in here.
Is it only gonna consume coal whenever there's things in range that it can use the thing on?
Or is it just gonna be a constant thing?
Oh, look at this!
It totally works!
Now we just need them to gather up at that point.
How do I do that?
Okay, so it's constantly going out and...
Okay.
And they're making babies.
That's fantastic.
Great, great, great.
Hmm...
I just had a thought.
We also need to make sure that...
When we do the killing...
That we only kill the adults.
Maybe a mechanism where...
You shoot arrows or something at a certain height.
So it's never gonna hit the ones that are too...
Small.
You know?
Something like that.
Or not arrows.
Could also be...
A drill, perhaps.
If it's like at this height, you know?
It's gonna hit the mobs that are adult and not the ones that are children.
Let's try that.
Let's do the...
Naive thing here.
Maybe we can even wire this up.
Somehow.
With the engine that we have going on over here.
Let me grab some shafts.
Some basic things.
Like that.
And maybe some wheels.
In fact, I think I'm gonna go disassemble this stuff out here now.
Taking all this with me.
Also, isn't it easier to...
How come I can't, uh...
Normally I can take things with the wrench, but it doesn't seem like I can do that now.
Weird.
Oh, I actually kinda like what I had here.
Oh yeah, there's this thing too.
Look at all these delicious components.
Finally cleaning up the mess here.
Okay, not bad.
Already looking better.
So obviously it ran out of food.
We need a...
How did you get out?
Unless you were out.
We need a way to automatically fill that with more weed, of course.
And maybe we can even wire that up with the farm over here.
So the weed that comes out of there is gonna go straight to here.
Ooh, think about that one.
That's pretty cool.
Now for the killing.
The drill needs...
I believe...
Yeah, it's from the back.
Okay.
So...
Let's go inside with this.
Don't need this right now.
And I get the coal.
Okay, so it consumed three coal during that.
Ideally we will connect like a windmill to this.
You know, this is just for testing purposes, of course.
Let's kinda feed them like that.
Um...
Hmm.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
I'm trying to think in stages.
Maybe I have...
Feeding area.
And then they somehow get led into the killing area.
They're trying to get out!
You can't!
Good luck!
So let's try this now.
I'm gonna put...
You know, wait.
That there.
And then from the back, we're gonna do this.
And...
Hmm...
That's probably a better way to do this.
If I take my...
Deployer...
Did I bring an extra?
Oh, let's just use this.
If I make this point down...
That could work, actually.
Except it's a little too low.
I really don't want these guys escaping.
Oh, why can I not make it turn the other way?
Okay, you know what?
Let's just test this for now.
Let's see if it actually only kills the adults.
This is the test I wanna make, anyway.
Turn it around.
There we go.
Let's see what happens.
Let's see if they walk into it.
This is the most naive test here.
Come on.
Oh!
Maybe if I...
Let me just lure them over here.
Okay, it does...
Okay, that works!
And is it gonna kill the children?
Dude, that is working beautifully!
And I don't think the kids are dying.
Let me feed these real quick.
Make some children so we can see.
I don't have any feed left.
Damn.
I mean, that works!
I think we got it!
I mean, over time, obviously, you know.
Now, they're gonna drop their meat, so...
We would like to have hoppers underneath.
I guess.
That would be the way to do it.
Hoppers that all lead to one output.
At least that's the Minecraft way to do it.
Maybe there's a better way in create.
Um...
Let's think about this.
We could also have...
Oh!
Once in a...
Okay, imagine now, if you will.
One, two, three, four, five, six drills at eye level.
Just like eye level ovens, except it's a killing machine.
And once in a while, it sweeps across like this.
Just kills everything in the path.
You know, and leaves the children unharmed.
And it happens on a timer.
Um...
That sounds so fucked up, man.
Something straight out of that movie with the ghost ship.
That was such a horrifying scene in that movie where they do something like that.
Yeah.
One thing first, though, we gotta get the wheat.
Wheat, wheat, wheat.
Man, it's really slow.
Wow.
This machine sucks.
Man, oh man.
It's gonna take a while.
Now, for the drilling idea, let's say we put them all on a line.
How am I gonna pull them all across?
Hmm.
Maybe like the...
The gantry carriage or whatever?
That's...
Is the first thing that comes to mind here?
Let's see.
Gantry.
Let me just search for it instead.
Gantry carriage.
Which...
I think I have that, actually.
Lying around somewhere.
Also, give me these.
We can even have a contraption control.
Nah.
We wanna have that automated.
It's not in here.
Rope pulley?
Maybe something there?
We pull it with rope.
Could also be an option.
Let me get this as well.
I cannot find what I need.
I may not have made it.
Am I blind?
It's not here.
Okay, well...
Gantry.
Casing.
Oh, we have this.
And the side casing.
Oh, here we go.
We didn't even make this.
Let's see.
Mm-hmm.
Along a gantry shaft?
Great.
That's exactly what I need, actually.
Gantry setups can move attached blocks.
Yes.
Meaning drills.
With the help of superglue, larger structures can be moved.
Power's gonna reverse direction?
Oh, it stops moving them.
Okay.
I just assumed.
Gantry shafts can have opposite orientations.
And what does that do?
Oh, that they move towards each other?
Oh, they even go sideways.
That's interesting.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Some rules apply for the propagated rotation.
Oh, they also have a...
Yeah, okay.
Oh, that's really convenient.
I think this is what I need to make.
Gantry, shafts...
I think I have some of those.
Eight!
I got eight of them.
Nice.
Gonna fix my food situation a little here.
Let's cook this.
Man, no, uh...
Okay, there we go.
I guess we don't need the milling machine and all that.
And this one, and that one, and this one.
Not right now, at least.
Oops.
What else do I not need?
Maybe that one?
Let's get these.
What does it take to make?
Okay.
Gantry, let's make eight more.
Sixteen.
Oops.
Let's go try it!
Let's just start putting some shit down.
Uh, let's do it.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, you little piece of shit!
Oh my god.
Wait, do I want it that way?
I think I want it the other way.
Come on!
There we go.
I lack some light here.
Okay, and now we put this on?
Sweet!
Alright.
Not bad.
I guess we want to make it that way now.
So it's actually the wrong way.
How do I change that?
Actually, it's fine!
Yeah, this is fine.
We need a linear chassis.
I guess it's a good one we can use for this.
I must have some leftovers.
There we go.
And obviously drills.
Don't think I have enough.
Actually, I do.
Because I have all these.
Fourteen.
Alloys.
Six, I guess.
Something like that.
We have eight in total.
That's probably a little too much.
The idea now is...
Like that, right?
And then on the end...
We're gonna have...
Drills.
Oh, man.
I do hate these fences.
Oh, my God.
Oh, this...
Okay, I mean, this is looking pretty ominous, in a way.
Let's try.
Shall we?
So, the way I understand this, we should just be able to do this.
Maybe spin the other way.
Maybe they do need...
Oh!
Oh, wait a minute.
Maybe they do need to be glued, then.
I thought because of linear chassis, they would just stick.
Uh-huh.
I've got glue.
It definitely worked, though.
Now it's stuck.
How do I turn it off?
I guess just do that.
I'll take the glue here.
What?
Oh, I just made that sticky.
I didn't want to do that.
Okay, there we go.
That should work.
Let's see.
Oh, look!
It doesn't kill the kids!
Nice!
And then we gotta find a way to make it go back and forth.
Hahaha!
Man, that's fucked up!
Uh, what's this?
Someone's sending me text messages.
Oh, shit!
Okay, someone's coming by with some...
Uh...
Window covers.
What is it called?
You know the thing you...
Blinds!
On the windows!
Right now, everyone can look through my windows.
It's still, like, very bare.
I just moved in, you.
Pretty much.
Okay, so...
This thing needs to be somehow reversed.
When I feel like it.
I could just click on it, but that's no fun.
We don't want that.
I guess we can set a timer, maybe.
Wasn't there, like, a block...
What was it?
Gearshift something?
Sequence to Gearshift?
Could be the one.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I timed the list of instructions.
Ah, but hold on a minute.
We also don't want to always kill the adults.
Because at some point...
We, uh...
We need to feed the adults.
So they can have kids before they get killed.
But I guess it's just a matter of...
Uh, frequency of feeding versus killing.
Configured sequence, huh?
Is that sequence loopable, though?
Or is it like a one-time thing?
Once finished, it waits for the next redstone signal and starts over.
Oh, okay.
So...
Alright.
Maybe we have a day-night timer on that.
You know, a daylight detector?
Once a day, it runs.
Alright.
Let me just try this.
Let's experiment.
Let's have some fun.
I'm gonna get the sequence to Gearshift.
See how that works.
And it's not that one.
It is...
I have it.
There it is.
Sequence Gearshift.
Let's see here.
I may need to ponder real quick on this again.
So you put it in between two shafts.
And then when there's power...
Right-click it to open the configuration UI.
Okay.
Aha.
Alright.
So that means we should put it at the end here.
Like this.
Then ideally, the motor...
here.
I'm just gonna do this because it looks better.
Oh, sick!
Wait.
Scroll to modify...
Okay.
Ah!
Well, I don't know how much I wanna turn it.
So we turn it 90.
Let's see what that looks like.
Let's just do that for now, actually.
I just wanna see.
Wait, what?
Is this angled wrong, maybe?
Why are you not working?
Oh, wait.
We need redstone power.
Redstone.
I'm just gonna use a lever for now, just to test.
But maybe I wanna put that on a...
on a daylight detector or something.
Maybe we put it up top.
Oh, can I even do that?
Yeah.
I can.
Okay, so 90...
Let's just see what that looks like.
Oh, that...
That was 90...
I guess that was 90.
Haha.
It's like nothing.
Brother, we need way more.
Somehow I have a feeling there's a better way to do this.
Let's see.
Oh, it only goes to there!
Oh, that's crazy.
Come on.
Oh, wait, no.
Oh, it stops briefly in between.
Okay, interesting.
So that was four, huh?
I don't like this one.
It's too fine-grained.
Maybe I'll just do some kind of thing where when it reaches the end, there's like an observer or something, and then it sends a signal to make it go the other way.
You know?
Because we do have a gearshift thingy that just reverses direction.
Like this one here, right?
Whatever that is.
I forgot the name of it.
Probably just this one, actually.
Gearshift.
And when there's a power on that, it just changes direction.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
That seems like a good one.
Let's just do it.
Super simple now.
Like that.
And we put this guy here.
And the motor at the end.
Now we just go like that.
It goes back.
Boom.
And then...
The other way.
It's beautiful!
Okay.
I wish there was a way to just stop this one.
Like, is it burning fuel right now?
I don't want you to burn fuel right now.
Let's just leave it there with no fuel.
Maybe I can control click on it or something.
Okay, so we have a working back and forth.
Um, this is like a guaranteed just kill everything button.
Now we need a way to pick up the items.
Let's see what we have at our disposal here.
Obviously we have a solution.
We can just use hoppers.
But maybe there's a better way.
Display board!
Wait, what?
I need to make that.
Gotta see what that's about.
An item drain?
Let's have like a drain for all the blood that can flow out after the killing.
It's so dark.
What would be smart?
Mechanical plow?
Wait, what is a plow anyway?
Did I make that?
Plow?
Why can't I see it?
Wait, what?
How come I can't see that here though?
Mechanical...
Oh!
It's because I'm not at a workbench.
I'm an idiot.
Let me check that out real quick.
There we go.
Well, I have all this.
Let's just make it.
Do I?
I don't actually have it.
Damn, iron sheets, huh?
I have one.
I guess I could quickly...
Ah, do I really want to?
Okay, let's just quickly press one.
Maybe we can connect it here even.
How does it work again?
On the side, okay.
This is the most scuffed thing...
Oh!
Oh, it's because opposite...
I see, I see, I see.
You can probably do it here then.
Nope, there's something in the way.
Where can I...
Extract some motion.
Come on.
This one.
There it is.
This is so scuffed.
We're gonna have a little, uh...
Thingy here.
Shit!
Alright, here we go.
Nice.
One more.
Stop!
Wait, I wonder how far down it goes.
Let's say we're to put that there.
Ah, it's not gonna extend all the way down there.
I'm not even gonna try.
That's stupid.
Dumb.
Plow.
Hey, I can make it!
There we go.
Let's ponder that.
Whenever plows are moved as part of the contraption...
It will break blocks without a solid collision hitbox.
Oh.
Inventories attached to the contraption will pick up there.
Okay.
Wait, it's like a minesweeper.
We put it in front of the tank.
Additionally, plows can create farm...
Whoa!
Hold up now!
That's kinda huge.
They can also launch entities without hurting them.
Okay.
Alright.
Wait a minute, this is exactly what I need.
I sweep this across the bottom to pick up all the items.
Hello?
There it is.
This is...
It's a little over...
You know...
Over-engineered, I guess, for my...
purposes.
But it works.
What else can I do?
So we have hoppers, we have the plows.
Two options that we currently have at our disposal.
Let me write it down, actually.
Find...
I also need a collection method.
Obviously...
Hoppers.
Plow.
Plows.
What else?
So items fall.
They...
They land on the floor.
All we need to do is have them be put into a box, right?
I guess we can have belts on the floor.
But is that gonna move all the animals to one side?
Probably, right?
Unless we have like...
One side going right, one side going left, and then right and then left alternating.
So that whatever items fall down, they will eventually make it to a box on either side.
Actually, that's a great idea.
Write it down.
Alternating...
Um...
Oh God.
What are they called?
Belts.
Underneath.
To transport items to...
Uh, chests.
Okay.
We have three methods now.
Let me just think, instead of browsing this.
So items fall on the floor.
We could also, somehow...
Um...
What could we do?
What can be used to collect items?
I mean, plows.
The plow is the obvious one.
Maybe chutes!
I mean, that's just another type of hopper, I guess?
Perhaps even cheaper to make.
Let me quickly see what that takes to make.
Ah, iron.
I don't have that.
Damn it.
Iron for everything.
Walker shafts.
There's also water, of course.
But that's...
I don't know about that.
That don't sound good either.
Item drain!
Wait!
That sounds exactly like what I need.
Item drains can extract fluids.
Oh, wait!
It's just fluids!
Is it?
When items are inserted from the side...
They roll across, emptying out their con...
Oh, okay.
Yeah, it is just fluids.
Okay.
That makes sense.
No!
W!
Um...
Okay, that's a no-go.
I got so excited for a second.
Item drain, you know?
Redstone requester.
Weird.
Portion spring.
Wait!
Portable...
Oh, that's the one I already made.
Maybe there's something there?
Wait, let me check the harvester again.
Oh, shit.
That's annoying.
Uh...
No, just show me here.
Harvester.
Ponder that.
Okay, so they obviously do this.
We know that.
But maybe they do other things.
Okay, so it's just crops.
It's just crops.
I guess.
Okay.
Item hatch?
No, that's the one to just deposit a bunch.
I mean, we already have three pretty good candidates here.
I should just pick one.
Turntable.
What's the...
Oh, shit.
Let's click.
Docking connector.
I
have no idea.
Maybe...
No, not packager.
Okay.
Let's just pick one.
Obviously, I think the hoppers are the obvious and easy solution here.
You know?
And it's not really that big a deal.
So we also need a feeding component here.
So...
The way to...
We can feed them from above, I guess?
Or we can even feed them...
What if we feed them when it goes the other way?
So we have like a deployer here on this side.
We feed them in one direction.
They grow.
We go back and kill them.
Feed them in one direction.
Grow.
Go back and kill.
Yo!
That's...
That's it.
That is too beautiful not to do.
That's amazing.
And the best part is, it's only gonna feed the big ones.
I need a shovel.
No, I don't.
I kinda do.
Also, do I not have more deployers?
I'm gonna make myself a shovel.
Out of...
Copper.
Oh wait, that's not part of this.
That came later.
Whoops.
Oh well.
Dang.
Uh...
I guess...
Ugh, fine.
I'll make it out of...
Iron.
I will have to go get some more though.
I think that much is confirmed.
So sticks.
There
we go.
Okay, we got a shovel now.
Then we need some more deployers.
I may already have all the ones I have.
Hmm.
Ah, maybe it's too much, actually.
Having, uh, the whole row of deployers.
Yeah.
Maybe let's not do that.
Let's just have a deployer on the side somewhere.
Like we had before.
Oh no.
We got children!
How did they hit me?
How do we do this, man?
So, we feed them first.
And we have to make sure that they're all fed.
Before we kill them.
Hmm.
I mean, we could just have...
Is it a bad idea?
Wait.
Maybe it's not that bad of an idea.
Let's say we have it like this.
And two more ideally, right?
But let's just, you know, space it out a bit.
Like this.
There we go.
These are the feeders.
And they should be feeding automatically because they're part of this moving thing, right?
Let's see if it works.
Ah crap, they're not connected by...
Yeah, okay.
Oops.
Uh, we need the...
Wait, what?
Okay, there we go.
Nice.
This should work now.
They do indeed feed.
Look at this.
It's killing the cow?
The cow survived.
How are you surviving?
Wait, I thought it was a guaranteed kill though.
Range of sticky sides.
What?
Oh!
Right, so if I make a structure on it, it's how far it extends.
Let's see.
Um...
Hmm...
I thought this would be a guaranteed kill when it moved across.
We need to move this slower.
That's the problem right now.
It's too fast.
So let's just attach a good old windmill to this bastard.
Or something like a water wheel.
Something simple that is like really slow.
I think I have one of those too.
Chain conveyor.
Wait, hold on.
Could this be used somehow?
Ooh, wait!
Let's grab some rotation from the windmill and use it here.
With chains!
Let's do that!
And then we can also try them out, right?
See how they work.
I'm excited for this.
Okay, so it comes from the top or bottom.
We have rotation here and it's quite fast.
We don't want the fast one.
Although we could just grab that.
Make it go out that way.
Here's a slower one.
This is a better...
This is actually perfect there.
Gearbox and then that way.
Could be a way to do it.
I like it!
So I'm gonna go ahead and gearbox...
There.
There it comes.
Let's have this there.
Ah, wait!
I need to put the shaft in first.
And then we cover it up.
And then out here, we're gonna use chains.
So we need a vertical gearbox now.
Like that.
Nice!
We rotate this guy?
Oh!
What was that sound?!
Oh my god!
Oh, I'm hanging on a chain I guess!
That's not what I want.
No, the other way!
Ow!
Can I not make it do that?
If I stand here...
Which way is it pointing?
Wait, I'm so confused!
Oh, maybe the chains just come out wherever you...
Oh, okay.
Wait.
So if I do this...
And I...
Let me read about this again.
Very weird.
Right-click two conveyors with chains...
Oh!
I see!
With chains!
Duh!
I thought maybe the chains were included!
Do I have any?
I may not have any.
So what, we just need one chain?
Let's see.
Also, how far can it go?
Cool.
Okay, now a chain.
Not holding enough.
Oh!
Ah!
I need no...
Okay, I see, I see.
Got it.
So it is not just like the belt.
You can go infinite with one belt.
No problem.
Really ought to go get some iron.
Very soon.
We need one more!
This is gonna look sick, by the way.
Wait, what?
I need...
Didn't it say eight before?
Now it says nine.
What the hell?
I'm being bamboozled.
Okay, now.
Surely.
Oh my god!
That's cool!
That is fantastic!
Look at this!
Ah, wait a minute.
We have a problem.
Wait a second.
Wait a goddamn minute.
Maybe that's how we kill the cows.
We push them into a wall until they become jelly.
Interesting.
I wonder if that was a one-off thing, or if it's consistent like that.
I need to grab this.
What don't I need?
Maybe we don't even need to drill!
Imagine!
Oh!
Wait a minute!
There's gotta be a way to scoop up items!
Imagine if we have a scooper that runs across like this, and we can somehow...
When it goes, like a vacuum.
That's gotta be a thing.
Maybe the chute?
The upward chute or whatever?
Come on, that's gotta be a thing.
Chute.
Let, uh, uh, uh, fucking...
Chute over here.
Show me.
Chute can transport items vertically...
Oh, okay.
From an inventory though.
Using the wrench...
A window...
Okay.
Yeah.
Ho!
Using encased fans at the top or bottom...
A chute can move items up...
Oh!
Wait a fucking second!
What if we use, uh, fans...
To move the mobs to one side where they get drilled from below?
But then we have to somehow make a filter to make sure that the kits don't get drilled.
Hmm.
How would I do that?
Otherwise, it's just gonna move everything over and kill everything.
That's bad.
Let's see what else it says.
Smart chute, uh, or vertical chute with additional control.
Huh.
How on earth...
Man, I love this thing.
Oh no!
Is it pulling me up?
Oh, kinda.
Look how nice this is!
I'm going on a ride.
But, the thing is, this one should be so fast now that these drills are gonna kill.
They will kill things.
The problem is, I ran out of test subjects.
They all died.
Crap cake.
Hmm.
This is a more difficult problem than I imagined it would be at first.
It really is.
Maybe I'm overthinking this, man.
Like...
So we feed them, we kill them, we collect them.
Right?
And...
To kill them, we have many ways.
Or to feed them, we have one way.
I guess, so far.
Which is the deployer.
Maybe we can be very inhumane about this.
What if we just put every animal inside a very small enclosure?
You know, we're talking maybe two by two.
And that's like the feeding area.
We feed them...
Until...
Some point, when there's enough.
And then we somehow transfer them to a killing area.
But that already sounds more complicated.
In a way.
Man, this...
Fucking hell, this is...
This is not an easy one.
Damn it all.
Tough.
I'm gonna put some of this stuff back here.
I don't feel confident now.
Put the dirt into...
This one, that one...
Oh, this one's full, huh?
Can we cook this?
In any case, I need more iron.
So, I have a proposal.
And the proposal is...
Let's go dig with our new machine.
The one that we know works.
For a fact...
Where did I put it?
The massive digging machine.
There it is.
Gonna grab this too.
There we go.
And...
Rails...
Are...
Not here.
I guess they're in the machine, at this point.
Some of them, at least.
Let's bring the glue as well.
And a shield.
I think that's pretty much it.
Let's see here.
Oh, I don't even have...
Oh, I can't even put it down.
Bro!
I must have a rail somewhere.
I can't believe that.
Where did the...
I don't understand.
Like, I had...
Ah!
There they are.
Thank God.
Beautiful.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
This one's ready, I think.
Like, everything here seems to be working.
I think we're ready to drill.
Now, how many do you have?
Thirty-five.
Okay.
Not great.
But...
It just means a little more often of a filling session.
Let's not use these, actually, if we're gonna go drill up here.
Normal stone.
Let's go do it.
I will bring a bed.
Or not.
No, let's not bring a bed.
We're gonna go in the mines anyway.
Oh!
We need torches.
That's one important thing.
Torches.
Uh...
Give me these.
Good enough.
We're gonna find some coal down there.
And we can make more.
Yep.
Probably don't need two stacks of these.
Okay, let's go.
Gone digging!
We're gonna dig in the mountain.
And we're gonna make a...
Huge.
Uh...
Working space.
We have to consider where we dig, though.
At what elevation.
Because...
Depending on the elevation, we get different things.
Here we're gonna get cobblestone.
And some iron.
And some of this...
Sink stuff.
And, you know...
But down there, we could potentially get diamonds and stuff.
So the question is, where do we want to do this?
I think I'll go a little further away from home.
In this direction.
And the good news is, we're gonna get and decide out of this too.
Yeah, actually.
Let's dig at this elevation first.
This is a good start.
We're gonna hollow out this frickin' mountain.
Let's do it here!
It's a great spot.
Wanna dance?
I'm in top form today.
You can't beat me.
Physically or mentally.
And here we go.
We're just gonna plop it down right frickin' here.
Gonna be glorious.
Look at that, man!
We even have some stuff in here.
Let's turn these into that, I guess.
Don't really want these.
Alright!
Here we go!
Oh, what's that?
Hold on.
What is this?
I think I'm ready!
And this one should already be...
Ready to go.
Excuse me.
We just push.
Should work.
And it goes on its own!
Let's not forget that part!
I forgot about that part, dude!
Oooh!
That's sick!
Oh my god!
I forgot we had that going!
Uh-oh, uh-oh, what's happening?
Fill it up, fill it up.
Okay, okay.
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
This is sick!
Oh my god!
It's so efficient!
Oh yeah, this is exactly what I needed.
And it's just going on its own, that's the best part.
And it's gonna collect coal right now, so we can keep having it go, you know?
There you go.
See, sometimes it's digging slower, because it's going through some heavier stuff, I guess.
Oh shit!
I destroyed it.
Wait, what did I do?
What did I do?
Whoops.
Is it working?
What have I done?
Oh no.
Ah fuck, what did I do?
How come it's not, uh...
What?
Huh?
I don't understand.
I don't know why it's not going.
Jesus Christ, look at how much it already collected.
Damn.
Fill it up.
Oh!
Wait, what?
Wait, 29?
Oh, I guess there's 30 in there now?
Bro, I have no idea how to...
Like, what?
How do I even fix this?
Like, I don't know why it's not working.
This makes no sense to me.
I have no idea what's going on.
What happened?
Why did it stop?
How do I get it back?
I may have to...
Oh my god.
Oh, I don't want to go back to do that.
Is there a way to get the torch?
Oh, actually...
No, I don't have redstone.
Is that the only way?
Can I not pick it up with the fucking wrench or something?
No, man.
That's pain.
That's pure pain.
I gotta go get a lever.
I don't see how else I can do this.
What an actual pain.
So you never want to leave home without a lever.
Imagine if I was, like, super far from home, what would I do, you know?
I don't even have one right here.
What does it take to make?
Lever for real, for real.
Wait, I can...
That's, like, super easy to make.
Go back.
Basically, I'm trying to figure out how to pick that shit up without having to use the damn minecart assembler.
Like, you know, I'm trying to be free of that thing.
I don't want it anymore in my life.
I thought I could do everything I always wanted to do with this wrench.
But I guess I was wrong.
I wonder if there's a limit to how big I can make this digging machine.
Like, let's say I wanted to make it ten times as big.
If it was still just work on one rail.
Or if it needed some more support or something.
Better fucking work.
Oh, thank God!
Thank the Lord Jesus above!
We're back in business.
Hold on.
Someone's calling.
Alright, I'm back.
Sorry about that.
The guy was here to deliver the blinds for the windows.
And I had to inspect the packages before I signed.
Here we go.
The dig must go on!
The tunnel must grow.
Shit.
But you can open those mid-flight?
That's crazy.
Man, I wonder if there's a way to...
So the next obvious thing we want to change about this thing is to have it automatically do the rail thing.
Because this is getting old.
It's too fast for me.
I can't keep up with it, you know?
Ah, let's just wait a bit more.
At least no lava yet.
Ooh, uh-oh!
Uh-oh!
Are we safe here?
It's making a bridge!
I'm ready to disassemble it, if shit goes south.
The gravel is being...
mined.
Look at this massive tunnel!
You know how long this would take?
If I didn't have this machine?
This would be a whole-day project!
Oh, it's full!
It's full.
I wonder when we're gonna come out on the other side, though.
Look at this massive tunnel.
This is something straight out of the back rooms, almost.
Just tunnels and tunnel and tunnel.
Let's go see what's in it.
Ooh!
Bunch of copper!
Some dripstone as well.
Kind of exciting inspecting these afterward, you know?
See what you got.
Got a little bit of andesite.
Not a lot.
Oh, actually, we also have a stack there.
Nice.
Obviously, the cobblestone is a bit problematic here.
Maybe there's a way we can throw that away automatically.
Because this is gonna get old fast, you know?
It's too much.
Something's flopping in the water.
Okay!
Not bad.
You know what?
Maybe this is the way to transport items.
Maybe we say, fuck the toolbox.
From now on, we just have a little contraption with us at all times with like a million chests on it.
Fill it up, pick it up, take it with us.
It feels like the ultimate sort of cheat or hack, you know?
I wonder why they run in circles like that.
Like, why are they programmed that way?
Oh my god, I'm getting a crazy headache in one eye.
Like, behind one of my eyes.
Mmm, hopefully it's not something bad.
Look at this cute little tunnel.
This was a 3x3, by the way.
Look how small it is compared to the other tunnel we made.
I'm gonna go back and try and improve this design.
Cause there's gotta be a way to somehow pick up those...
rails automatically, and put them back in the chest.
I just...
There's no way I'm gonna keep doing that rail thing.
Back to the drawing board.
This is the next logical step.
We should probably have a little...
thingy here.
There we go.
Why'd it turn that way?
That's so weird.
Oh well.
Okay, let's think about this.
Uh...
So this is the one with the rails.
Wait, I...
I just had a problem...
arise in my mind.
If we have a deployer...
No wait, there is a way to feed that...
with items.
Cause we do that over here.
Right?
We have that going on right over here.
Yeah, look.
We have a funnel on this one.
And then we had a belt.
But maybe we don't need a belt.
Maybe we can do with...
Maybe a simple...
A humble hopper...
will do the trick here.
I may actually cannibalize a hopper.
For my nefarious purposes.
Ah, but wait a minute.
We need to bring it up, I guess.
So...
Uh...
There was a chute that brought things up, right?
But only if you had a fan underneath.
So that would be kinda weird.
Uh...
Also, how would I even pick this up?
Let's think about that for a sec.
Maybe that's the first thing we need to solve.
Is it as simple as a deployer...
With a...
Pig axe on it?
Let's try.
The deployers are outside.
I shall be grabbing this.
Da da da da.
There we go.
Let's give it my axe.
And my axe!
Uh...
Let's just try it.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's gonna dig my fucking house.
We can't do that.
Shit.
Wait, did that...
No, no, no, no, no.
Back up, back up.
Also...
Connect those.
And...
Remove the...
Oh!
Um...
We wanna turn this bastard around!
How do I...
I guess I can do it if I'm really fast.
That's the only way.
Got it!
Okay!
Then, uh...
Let me do this.
Stop...
Stop turning around!
Lock it!
Okay, now.
Ah, fuck!
No!
Bro, what is this crap?
Oh, wait!
Oh, I see.
That's why.
Turn it off.
There we go.
Done it.
Okay, good.
Now...
Now that that's done...
Let's see if it'll remove the...
Thing as it goes.
And, you know what, actually?
Instead of having the power, let's do the non-powered version.
Just for this testing.
Yup!
It's not working.
Unfortunately...
So how do I do that?
Maybe it needs to be one further down.
That could be a thing.
Like, one further down.
Oh my god, I need this pickaxe.
Okay.
There you go, sir.
Ah!
It's not...
Damn.
Gotta glue it.
Wait, what the...
Uh...
I think that works.
This is so not optimal.
Bro, sir...
What is happening here?
Oh no!
What now?
What's...
What's going on?
What the...
Oh...
My god...
Get on the rail.
Please.
What's wrong with it?
It's connected.
Hello?
What am I missing?
Redo it all.
And then here.
There.
That should work.
Okay, so it's not actually removing the damn rails.
Oh, man.
Also, what's this?
Get rid of it.
Hmm.
Okay.
Uh...
Maybe there's no way to do this, actually.
I need something that breaks a block.
Maybe a saw?
A saw can do that.
Oh, wait, no.
Maybe just a drill, actually.
Wait, is it that simple?
Hold on a minute.
Drill, drill, drill.
Where did I put that?
That breaks blocks, right?
Oh, wait a minute.
We also need a way to collect it.
Ooh, hold up.
So we break it and then collect it.
Uh...
Shit.
Hoppers.
Wait, I can use plows, I guess.
Wait, that even breaks them!
That actually breaks and...
collects.
Hold up a minute.
Ooh, wait.
This is totally it, though.
Give me the axe.
Give it back here.
Okay.
Get rid of this.
I guess it would have to be...
Oops.
Oh, my God.
Will you stop?
Christ.
It's because I'm used to this being on three.
It's killing me.
Uh...
Glass!
We need more glass.
Actually, maybe a slab is what the doctor ordered.
Hmm.
And glass.
Check it out.
We're gonna do...
Uh...
This.
Yeah.
Wait, that doesn't even work.
Wait, is that gonna move across the ground, though?
Like, with this thing?
That's a little...
Also, ideally, I wanna turn this around.
So I can scoop up the damn...
Rails, as we go.
Uh...
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Even better.
Oh, my God, that's beautiful.
And then we just need to somehow...
Uh...
Funnel it up there.
Maybe literally with a funnel.
Okay.
Let's see what we got at our disposal here.
Let's bring a funnel.
And maybe chutes.
What is nozzle?
Uh, no, not that one.
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh.
Shoot me.
Bro, didn't I have, like, a lot of chutes?
Oh, let's...
I have an idea.
Uh...
Item transportation.
There we go.
Let's see.
Oops.
Shoots can transport items vertically from and to inventories.
That sounds exactly what I need.
Using the wrench, a window can be created.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, okay, good decoration.
Got it.
So now it's going down.
Don't tell me it's only with a fan.
Okay.
Placing shoots targeting the side, faces of another will make it diagonal.
And they all fall down.
Is it really a fan?
Okay.
Wait, let me actually quickly read about the, uh...
This one again.
Whenever plows are moved as part of an animated contraption...
But can I just put a chest or something and let it collect automatically?
Inventories attached to the contraption...
Well, there it is!
Dude!
Okay, it's much easier than I thought.
So wait, this literally should just work?
Except, I don't know, this...
This makes me feel weird.
I would say here we would need a slab.
Just so it doesn't, you know...
I feel like, yeah.
Right.
Okay, um...
Now, let's collect it...
Or do this.
Except we probably don't have enough of this now.
There's no way this works.
Why can I not push it from the back, dude?
Is there a way I can make it pushable from the back?
Like...
This is so...
That's such an annoying problem.
Movement...
What was this?
Oh, the creation of moving...
Oh god, I don't even know.
I think I need to touch the...
Thing down here for it to move.
Which is super annoying.
And...
Okay.
Ooh!
Okay, okay.
So why didn't it work?
I may have to redo the entire fucking...
Gluing.
It's so weird.
The glue stuff just...
Oh shit.
Breaks my brain, man.
Get rid of it all.
Okay, we're clean now.
Good.
And then...
There we go.
That should work.
I think we're in business.
And...
Then we do...
Oh, there it is.
Oh, it's...
It...
Aha!
Yeah, right.
It's doing that.
That's funny.
But why is it not going?
Do we need to...
Oh, wait.
This one is in the way now.
Technically.
Oh, that's awkward.
Get on the rails.
Does it have rails?
Oh!
Ah!
Ooh!
I see the problem.
It's removing the rail it's sitting on.
Ah!
Shit.
I get it.
That's bad.
Okay, stop it.
Stop it.
And now it turned around.
Because...
Reasons.
So this design is not gonna work.
We're gonna have to move it back even one more.
Fine.
I'll do it.
It's just gonna make it even more annoying to push though.
Like...
That's my biggest thing right now.
That's...
Pissing me off.
And...
That should just work?
Hey, you know what actually?
What if we were to put the...
I mean, we don't have to have the thing here.
You know?
We could put that maybe back here.
Although it feels weird balance-wise.
It's gonna tip over almost, right?
Uh...
You know what I mean by this?
Like...
Instead of this, we're just gonna put...
No, then this one cannot...
Oh, actually, yeah!
Oh, oh yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is gonna work.
Let's just do this.
Like...
Oops.
Let's say the minecart is...
Oops, here.
Oh, this is such a mess.
Right?
It's just gonna be there.
But...
Wait.
Then the design is really weird now.
Do we really need to be...
Wait a second.
Hold on.
No, no, no!
Wait, wait!
This is not gonna work!
Because it's gonna...
It's gonna remove the rails in front of it.
Whoops.
That's dumb.
Not even gonna work.
I don't know what the fuck I'm smoking here.
Back to the old design.
You didn't see that.
It never happened.
Turn this the other way, please.
There we go.
Actually, I guess for now we can have it like that.
So this is still relevant.
And then this one here.
And then the glue situation is...
Alright, it seems.
So all we gotta do now...
Push...
But how do I fri- Oh, it's so annoying, man!
Push the damn thing!
How the fuck?
Can I push it?
I could ju- Maybe I just put it straight on.
Like that.
And that should work.
So now we're gonna start it.
Lever.
Do I not have a lever?
Nice!
We got a- Okay, we got the whole thing now?
Are you ready to witness a miracle?
Cool.
I'm actually so confident it's gonna work.
I'm gonna go straight to the...
I'm gonna go straight to the mines.
You'll see.
This one should be it.
This one should just go.
And only be limited by coal.
Or a power source.
Wait, speaking of...
No, it's- No, no, no, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was about to say, we need the generator, but no we don't.
Because we have the minecart with the f- With the fountain, I was about to say, furnace.
Let's put it over here now.
All we need to do at this point...
Is to put down...
Uh, wait.
One, two, three...
Four, so I guess here...
Wait, are the rails part of the- Hold on, something's off.
Uh, yeah.
This is not gonna work.
Something's off here.
We got some problem.
Yeah.
That needs to go.
But, do we even know if this is really connected now?
Is it, like, fake connected?
Hope it's not fake connected.
Also, this thing may need to be a slab.
I don't trust like that.
Put a slab in, instead.
This should work.
Now.
Put the damn thing on here.
We're gonna need a lever there.
Take it with us.
Turn it around.
Remove it.
Not that we needed to do that, but okay.
Um...
And...
Are you ready?
Shouldn't that just go?
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Hold on a minute.
Do we know if it's getting fed in here?
Maybe this one is not getting fed.
Ah!
Hold on.
Rail's here.
Unless this one automatically takes from the chests?
I don't think that's gonna happen.
Is it?
Wait.
Let me put one chest...
Or one in there.
And then three here.
Oh, it had 34 inside.
Alright, okay.
Also, I think we need some power here.
Oh my god, I have a silk touch pickaxe.
I can't even mine this shit!
That's so triggering.
Is it...
Does it not have coal?
Don't do this to me.
Fill it up with this.
You gotta be kidding me.
Oh my god, dude.
I gotta go all the way fucking back to my base.
Cause I can't mine the coal!
That is so rage inducing.
Oh my god.
This... kills...
the crab.
Wow.
At least there's calm music to accompany me in these troubling times.
Um...
Oh nice!
I got 39 coals.
This better be the thing I need.
I swear to god, this digging machine has been a straight nightmare from start to finish.
This better work right now with such precision and elegance that...
Everyone starts to weep of joy.
Including myself.
This better be the most cathartic moment of all time.
When this coal goes in...
Wonders will be seen.
And heard across the ocean...
To distant civilizations and all that.
Fill in the rest.
Here we go!
As soon as I right click on this thing right now...
All our problems will be solved.
It's...
Okay, stop.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
It's not feeding.
The feeding is not real.
So...
Wait.
Isn't that an easy fix?
We just put the chest on top.
Right above it.
That sounds easy.
With a hopper.
Ayy!
Right?
Also, we need to disassemble here.
Put this bag over here.
One, two, three, four.
That way.
Now!
We're gonna relocate these chests.
Or maybe just one of them.
Doesn't really matter.
Wait a minute now though.
Is that even gonna work?
That doesn't seem like it's gonna work.
Wait, the...
Oh, it's...
It works!
Alright.
It just...
It works.
Ah, but this...
Okay, that's an issue right there.
We're not gonna dig that high.
I see the problem.
Maybe we do a sideways...
Operation here.
Wait, that's not gonna work either though.
Unless...
This counts as a chest...
And it gets filled up automatically...
As we go.
Also...
Wait.
I need to make sure that this one is only getting fed...
Rails.
We need a filter.
Ah, hold up.
Hold the freaking phone.
Why is it peeping?
Or...
Leaking.
Oh, this is pain.
I need to look at...
I mean, there's definitely filters everywhere.
Can I...
Can I just go like filter?
Matches items against a set of attributes or categories.
Can be used in filter slots of creates components.
Ah, wait a minute.
I need a...
I need one of these with a filter slot on it.
So that's the other version, I believe.
Damn.
Gotta go back again.
We need the...
Not the anticide, but...
Brass, I believe.
Actually, let me just double check.
Brass...
Funnel?
Let me see.
Anticide funnels can only ever extract single items.
Yeah, but look.
You see the filter thing here?
It has a filter thing.
Or does it?
Yeah.
Look, this one doesn't have it.
We need the brass one.
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Maybe we need a chute.
Or something.
Funnels, yeah.
Oops.
Pulls items from the inventory.
Placed while sneaking, it puts items into the inventory.
Oh my god, this is so overwhelming, dude.
There's just so many different fucking components.
It's crazy.
Oh my god.
Like, I have no idea where to start with this.
Like, I guess I need a brass funnel that I change direction on.
And then I need...
Uh...
A chest.
Wait, does it just connect like that?
I don't know.
Like, there's so many unknowns here, man.
Shit!
Let's try something simple first here.
Change direction.
Put a chest.
Oh, fuck.
Say what now?
What's this?
And it's like a tunnel.
What's the difference?
What about the auger stuff?
Uh...
I don't...
Okay, hold on.
Smart chutes.
Items.
Items in the filter slot specified.
Okay.
Good.
I mean, that's kind of what we need.
But it needs to be...
Horizontal.
It's such a stupidly simple problem.
And there's like a million different things I can try, and I don't know which one is correct, you know?
It is so overwhelming.
Um...
I guess we can maybe...
Put a chest here.
And then we have to bring it in there.
Uh...
I have no fucking clue, bro.
I think I'm just gonna make one of each of the components and just, I guess, try all of them.
See what works best.
The good news is I have most of them.
I just gotta pick them up.
Um...
So I would need...
Let me see what I did here.
Yeah, I mean, this is using belts, right?
This is not what I need right now.
Okay.
I guess I gotta make some chutes.
We're gonna try the chutes, and we're gonna try...
Uh...
What's it called?
Maybe a specific type of funnel.
The brass funnel?
Gimme those.
And...
What else?
Brass funnel!
Fantastic!
I even have it.
Incredible.
Just one.
And that's pretty much it.
That's what I wanted to test right now.
My inventory is atrocious!
Keep the glass.
Oh, wait, wait!
I need to check something else.
Let me just do a quick search for filters again.
Matches items against a collection of items...
No, okay, that's not it.
Smart chute!
I think I may have one of those.
Uh...
Smart chute...
Don't have it.
Let's just try this.
Weirdly, like, this is, like, headache-inducing, except it's actually removing my headache, weirdly.
I had a headache before, it's kinda going away working on this thing.
That's counterintuitive.
That doesn't make any sense right now.
But hey!
It works, so that's good.
So the problem right now is that...
Everything is working except for the fact that the deployer needs to be fed...
Some...
Items.
Right?
And it's not being fed.
I'm gonna put that...
Let me see here.
Funnel.
Change direction.
And now we have a filter.
I wonder if funnels are only meant to work with belts.
Because if I put this here...
Oops.
Oh no.
Where did it go?
Here we go.
Like, it's just...
Actually, maybe it's fine.
Maybe this works.
Who knows?
Put it in.
No?
Okay, let's try something really naive.
Just put it right next to it.
No?
What if I pre-feed it?
Maybe it's, like, a thing from left to right?
Like, if I put rails there...
Maybe something happens.
Lock rotation.
And it's being filled up.
I mean, this is working at least.
The problem is it's not being fed.
That's, like, it's just gonna stop.
After a while.
Fucking hell, man!
But hey, it's working.
At least this part.
When is it stopping?
Wait, what?
Wait, look at this!
It's...
It's taking it, I think.
Somehow, someway, it's just...
Working?
Why?
Okay, well, I...
Alright, you know what?
I totally overthought this one, I guess.
Look at the glory of this!
Just limited by coal!
Fill her up!
Oh my goodness!
Okay, so...
What is the lesson that we learned here?
When you're dealing with a contraption like this...
Logic goes out the window.
And we enter into...
Into fantasy magic land.
Where everything just works.
Don't even think about it.
It just works.
As soon as we're not in a contraption...
Logic has entered the game again.
Another lesson...
When you're dealing with a contraption...
If you're starting to think about how to solve something...
It's probably already solved.
Which doesn't make sense, but...
Do you know what I mean?
We even get experience from all this.
Oh, man!
It's working!
You know what the best part is?
We probably just need two rails for this then.
We don't even need like 38.
Look at this.
I'm taking all this now.
Gimme.
Ah, it stopped!
Okay, so maybe we need to...
Wait, hold on.
What happened?
Oh, you need to go on the rail again, I guess.
There we go!
And now it's going.
Oh, what?
Okay, maybe it needs a little more than the rails I had.
That's fine, though.
Let's just put it down.
Alright.
Go off, sweet prince.
Do your thing.
You can have a bunch of rails.
It's fine.
This is incredible!
Oh my god.
Oh, you know what this means probably?
That this one's going to be filled automatically too.
Like this is going to keep taking cobblestone or whatever stone we have.
It just works.
Just like...
Is it Todd Howard?
Who says that?
It just works.
Except it stopped working.
Why?
What happened?
It just does not work, apparently.
What do we hit?
The hell?
Okay, maybe there is something about the left side.
Like, I was totally just saying shit when I did that, but is it really that?
No way.
This one is...
Okay, you have some now.
Wait, why...
The fuck?
Why is it not working now?
Yeah, it's not...
It's not plopping it down for some reason now.
Wait, what the...
This is a...
This is a fragile machine, man.
Like, what is going on here?
Push it back onto the...
I need to understand exactly how this...
Okay, so it's placing the rails now.
It's the removing, yeah?
Yeah?
And let's see what happens here.
Oh shit!
Wait, is it gonna cope?
Nope!
It doesn't work with water.
Got it.
So that's the next problem we gotta solve.
Make it waterproof.
IP6 or whatever it's called.
Where's the water coming from?
Oh, it's coming from here.
Oh no, will you stop that?
So, the thing that happens now is that the water...
makes it so...
you can't put down the rail.
Right?
Oh wait, but I have a solution for that though.
Watch this.
I know how to solve this puppy.
We're gonna put little...
fences.
We need fences that go down like this...
and block water from entering from the sides.
You see what I mean?
Or doors.
Maybe the door technique.
But that's not really...
That doesn't sound great, does it?
But if we do like...
Oh my god.
Actually, I don't want to mess with it right now.
Let's just keep digging.
I like to dig.
Keep digging.
Let's just go.
If... oh no, what now?
Why... why you no work?
You run out of... oh, you ran out of coal?
No.
Oh wait, am I feeding that one out of...
I'm confused.
It's working again now, I think.
Yeah, now we're back to working.
This is a fragile machine, man.
Oh, we're full.
So, stop.
Okay, so the next step is to...
make it so that this one does not pick up cobblestone.
Or at least, uh, it...
throws out cobblestone as we go.
Right?
So, check it out.
We're gonna do this.
Uh, this is actually an easy fix.
Is that...
Did I...
I think I left behind...
the...
assembly...
mechanism.
Look how far down this tunnel it is!
Hot damn, we dug a lot!
I can't wait to get the train!
Imagine having trains through this tunnel!
It's gonna be so sick.
Dude, we're even gonna make a machine that creates a tunnel and lays down train tracks behind it as we go along.
I mean, I'm already thinking way ahead, of course.
First, we gotta get a train.
Otherwise, we can't really do much.
And when are we coming out the other side of this mountain?
That's what I wanna know.
Maybe we're actually so deep that we won't.
At some point, surely, right?
Okay, check it out.
This is an easy fix.
Here.
Push it in.
Whoa, that's...
That messed me up a little bit there.
We are gonna put a brass funnel right there.
We're gonna switch the direction that way.
And put a little filter.
Oh, shit.
There you go.
Wait, why is it not emptying?
Is it because there's no space to empty?
Ah!
Okay, yeah, that's it.
The only annoying thing about this is, I'm gonna have...
I'm gonna probably pick it up as I go.
Which is...
Unless I stay on the right side.
And I wonder if this...
Well, this...
This one's not gonna...
Do that, I guess.
Unless it's gonna take from here at some point.
Is it that intelligent?
Let's see this...
Let's say this one is empty.
Right?
Like, we throw all this away.
Like that.
And we pick this up.
Ah, okay, it's not gonna do that.
But!
I know what to do.
Easy fix.
You ready?
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
I guess that would happen.
Where did the chest go?
Oh, no.
Bro, where did the chest go?
Oh, it's right here.
I had it.
I wonder if this stays connected, though.
Like, does this even work?
That may not work.
Wait, I'm so dumb.
Why not just have the chest on one side, bro?
Oh, man.
Just...
Just make a double chest.
Just have one chest!
Ah, double chest.
Would be better.
Like that.
And then...
Hell yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
And then we put the glass back.
Then we remove this guy.
Hell yeah.
There it is.
Oh, did I just throw away my shovel?
Ah, no.
It's gonna be impossible to retrieve that without collecting...
Wait, no.
Maybe I didn't.
No, I did.
I did.
I see it.
This is a nightmare.
Nightmare.
This is something you would see...
In a straight-up horror movie.
You know?
This is what nightmares are made of.
For sure.
Whew!
Okay.
Fill this up with the rest.
And now this should work, right?
So...
Here we go.
We're gonna grab this.
We're gonna lever.
Uh, this one is pointing that way.
That's good.
Lock that shit.
Turn it on.
No.
Turn it off.
Take this guy.
Put it there.
On.
Pick it up.
Ah!
We were so close.
Pain.
Oh, no.
No, bro.
No.
Yes.
Yes, bro.
Wait, what?
Oh, right.
No!
We're fine.
There we go.
Now.
Boom.
Fixed.
Oh, wait.
There we go.
You ready?
Boom.
And...
There it is.
And now...
For my next trick.
Did this...
Oh, wait.
That was...
I'm not gonna pick it up.
I don't give a shit.
Too much...
You know...
Pain.
Too much pain.
Okay.
You ready?
Here we go.
This should eject...
The cobblestone...
Automatically.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Fill it up.
No!
Damn it!
Back on.
Yes.
We're back in business.
The dig is real.
And this time...
Look at it.
Ejecting...
Trash on the...
Oh, that's actually so cool!
Hell yeah!
Yeah!
Maybe we can even make it...
Plop down...
Lights automatically as we go along.
Wait, can I put a light on the machine itself?
That's a question, isn't it?
Oh my goodness.
Now this...
Oh, wow.
This is a long tunnel.
And I can probably inspect the chest as we go.
Woo!
Not a lot of iron though.
Finding a lot of copper here.
What happened now?
Why doesn't it work anymore?
What the fuck?
Wait, no.
I don't understand the logic here at all!
Okay, so watch.
It gets filled up, but why isn't it being consumed?
As we go.
So, at approximately 40, it should start...
Hopefully going down as well.
Oh!
Jesus Christ, that noise was loud.
Wait, what's happening there?
40!
And it stopped!
Maybe it's about where...
Like...
Where it is exactly in here.
You know, like, classic hopper behavior.
Uh, let me fill this up now.
I need more.
Also, why is my inventory, like, filled with...
Random...
Shit.
Now it's in the first slot.
Maybe it's gonna take from there now.
I forgot where I had it before when it worked.
Okay, the moment of truth.
We're so close to having mastered this thing.
Here we go!
It's working!
So that was it.
It needed to be in the first slot.
Oh my, there's so many small nuances.
Oh, we're outside!
We're outside!
We made it through!
No!
Oh glory!
Wow!
That's so cool!
Oh my god.
Guys!
I think we're ready for the nether!
This thing has proven itself!
We are ready to go to the nether.
This is indeed the machine that shall conquer the underworld.
Give me this.
Can't have crimes here.
Not on my watch.
Incredible.
Wow.
Ah, you know what?
It's all worth it.
This is an incredible feeling.
I've gotta get revenge!
Oh, I've gotta fucking strip the nether of all its resources.
It's gonna be so good.
What joy.
We're gonna find so much netherite.
Now, last time the netherite situation was that apparently it didn't get picked up in the nether.
Which is still confusing me.
Because why shouldn't it be picked up like everything else?
Like, it's an item that has been mined.
Isn't that weird?
Maybe I just happened to be close enough that I picked it up with my body.
Before the machine did.
That is, that is a possibility.
So, we'll see.
Oh, and in the nether, we're also gonna have the ejector on the sides filter out the nether rack.
So that we only keep the good stuff.
You know?
Man, that was such a big-ass tunnel over there.
Oh, I wish I had my spyglass.
We're gonna make another one.
And then hopefully soon...
Man, imagine if the netherite is the thing I need to make the train.
That would just be so beautiful.
I feel like I've tried almost every other block at this point, you know?
Well, not everything, but a lot.
Okay.
Let me empty the chest, I guess.
On this glorious machine.
Oh yeah, dirt.
I guess it's picking up that too.
Let me empty my inventory.
Put all the create stuff away.
Ah, this one I'll need.
I will bring the wood.
I don't want to bring the glass.
Tripstone, that's definitely stone, of course.
I think we need a stone three.
This will be stone three.
Coal, we're gonna bring that, of course.
Beaver, also.
Don't even think I need a toolbox at this point.
But I guess it's nice to have.
Dude, all this copper?
Wait, I figured out a reason why you don't want to blast copper.
You're not gonna get experience from it.
That's, that's the trade-off.
You can bulk blast all of this, but you're not gonna get the experience.
Right?
Because this right here is a lot of experience just sitting.
So, really, this is what I want to use.
And I should probably put a hopper on that.
I must have one.
There we go.
Filled it up completely.
And blast the shit out of it.
We're gonna take half of this with us.
Ah, maybe 23 is probably good.
But it seems like you can only use coal.
Or at least you cannot use wood.
On the furnace and minecart.
Kinda want to put more in here now, but there's no room, so...
Whatever.
Exotic...
That's not an exotic fence.
That's a pretty normal fence.
Everything else is ready.
The only limitation right now, I would say, is my amount of food.
We should go fix that right now.
Like, I was gonna try and do it with the automated cow killing machine.
Problem is, I can't do it.
I just don't have the skill for it right now, or the mental capacity to put it all together.
This is the best I could come up with here, with the gantry.
And the, you know, the killers on the side that move across.
It works at killing, but I still need to collect and, you know, all that other stuff.
Wait.
I do wonder though, if I use a plow, and I sweep across, maybe the plow will also kill animals.
Yeah.
We're gonna have to try that later.
But right now, I'm just gonna go out there, and I think I'm just gonna kill some cows.
Or...
No.
Dude, what if we made, like, the biggest frickin' bread farm of all time?
Like, okay, this, what we have up here, it's working, but it's, like, super tiny.
We need something big, Gandalf.
Huge.
You know?
Ultimate breadage.
Uh...
What would be the best way to do that?
Nah, you know what?
No.
Not yet.
Later.
Although I do need food.
So, I need to do something, man.
The food situation in Minecraft is killing me, literally!
I'm dying from lack of food!
How the hell...
I feel like we need to solve this problem now.
Like, I can't go on like this.
This needs to be solved right now.
We also need to grab some more cows, because I ran out of test subjects.
I got wheat.
Uh, we can...
Okay, you'll be my test subject for this.
No, wait, you're too small.
Yeah.
It's not gonna work.
I feel like it's too hard.
Like, it's just too hard.
Okay, so, remember when this thing moved the other way, and it sort of squished the cow against the side?
Check this out.
What if...
What if we made this enclosure, like, super tiny?
Like, from here to here.
There's just this tiny little area.
And we just keep...
Hmm, wait, let me think.
Yeah, actually.
It's genius.
Oh my god!
I figured it out, guys.
Check it out.
I got it, I got it.
This is super simple, actually.
It's gonna work, too.
It's gonna cost almost nothing.
Uh...
Wait, we don't need this.
We don't even need these drills!
I think.
We don't need these, either.
Maybe we do need those.
That's maybe the one thing we do need.
And this thing needs to move the other way, I guess.
No, we need this guy over here.
Give me this.
I'm also gonna clean this up here to make it look nicer.
This is gonna be super inhumane and horrible for the animals, but...
That's what it is.
Can't be helped.
Wait, why don't even...
I can make it even smaller.
Uh...
Okay, let's not go too crazy.
Like, I...
I don't wanna be a bad guy, you know?
Basically, my idea is this.
We put the animals in here.
Make it so that there's almost no room.
And then, once in a while, I click a button.
Gym.
You know?
And this thing moves across.
Squishes everyone into death.
Moves back.
And then, because we have such a little area...
We don't need...
We only need a couple hoppers.
And boom.
Bob's your uncle.
That's it.
Sounds simple, right?
That's pretty much it.
In fact, let's make this a little shorter.
Don't need this.
They're gonna be squeezed like that.
Uh...
We're gonna move this over.
In between here, we're gonna put the...
Gearshift.
And then this guy.
And we're gonna put this guy.
And we take the chains.
And we cut...
Oh!
Look at all these chains that fell off.
Boom.
Then we need a lever.
Squished!
Everything gets collected.
Hoppers underneath.
Incredible.
Or even better.
Maybe we don't need hoppers here.
Because...
Hoppers are expensive.
Maybe chutes...
Will do trick.
What's up, Chuty?
We even make four at a time.
You know?
So, chutes.
You know what?
We can even make the enclosure smaller.
Let's make it...
Like...
Insanely small.
Right?
And...
Oh!
Uh...
But we do need one way to feed them automatically.
Let's not forget that part.
This needs to be...
Oh!
That's...
This is also fixed by the small enclosure.
Oh my god.
Look at this.
We're gonna make it even smaller.
Right?
Like this.
And then on this side, we're gonna be feeding them...
Oh!
It's so weird and fucked up, man.
It's horrible.
And...
I think...
No.
I want the feeder to be at least this high.
So that I don't feed the little guys.
You know?
They don't need food.
There we go.
Fill her up with wheat, as they say.
And...
Now...
Wait, is that even gonna work though?
Maybe this is too high.
This may not work.
We gotta bring in a cow.
To experiment.
Hey cow!
There's gotta be one on the loose nearby here that ran away from earlier.
Chickens are too tiny.
We can't use them.
Could also use a sheep.
Anything will do.
And...
Nobody?
Anyone?
Bueller?
Come on.
Daddy needs to experiment.
And you're getting free food.
Ah, here we go.
You come with me.
Come here.
Oh yeah.
I know you smelled this.
You smelled it.
You smell it?
You smell...
Oh, I'm gonna take your friends too.
Look at this.
We're gonna have a party.
Everyone's invited.
Maybe I should make some leads.
Make this process easier.
Come on now.
Painfully slow.
Come on, come on.
Come with me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I guess pork chops will have to do.
I mean, that's also nice.
Don't need to have steaks right now.
This is a fine test.
What is that demon dog?
Fucking trying to kill my sheep.
Did you see its eyes?
It was red.
What the heck, man?
Come on now, guys.
I've got a surprise for you.
You're going into a tiny, tiny, but amazing enclosure.
It's weird how this is approximating real life, you know?
Oh!
Oh my god, the most efficient way to kill animals is to put them in a very small space.
Okay.
Follow me!
I know you want to get in this little area here, don't you?
Come on.
Interesting.
Let's push him in.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Come on, come on, come on!
Fuck!
Maybe it's too small.
Can't even get him in there.
Alright, come on now, come on now.
You made it a bit big, a bit bigger.
I can't speak English.
You, you.
Look what I got.
Come on, then.
Too smart for their own good.
Got you, got you!
You're mine.
Stay put.
Now, breed.
Oh wait, I should have done it with this to check.
Oh my god, I'm an idiot.
Whoops.
Dang.
Oh man.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe we bring the feeder to the other side.
Because this is where the rotation is.
In fact, there's one right there we can use.
So we just need a gearbox right now.
Gearbox.
Yeah!
We also gotta make that gantry a little, a little, um, wider.
Gantry shaft.
And box my gears.
Do I have one?
Vertical.
Could become a normal.
There we go.
Actually, bring both.
Just in case.
Now, maybe there's a way to make this even smaller now, the enclosure.
Like, all we need to do is to bring, get them in here.
Like, look at this right now.
I can do it, I can do it.
Hit the little guy!
Yeah!
Ooh, life sucks now, doesn't it?
This is not good.
For you, I mean.
Uh, let me, should we try this?
It's gonna kill them all though!
Maybe we wait until there's at least two children.
So they can have babies.
Or, you know, grow up and be grown-ups.
Uh, gearbox.
Uh, do you mind moving away?
Thank you.
And then...
Move away...
Oh no!
I...
What happened?
It popped!
It's gone!
Somehow it's gone from my inventory.
No, it's here.
Oh my god, what the...
Got it!
And then we turn it?
No.
Yes.
It's...
Okay, uh...
We need the glue.
Right.
Uh...
Let's see here.
So that is the one...
That needs to go...
Here.
And then...
We also gotta bring this...
Abba, wait.
That's not even gonna...
Abba, that's fine.
This is fine.
This should work.
So are they being fed?
That's the question.
We gotta wait to see this.
I mean, I think they're already full.
Let me...
Let me check if they're full.
I guess I can check that by doing this.
If I...
Yeah, I can't...
I can't right-click them, so they're full.
We gotta wait.
Uh, in fact, a better way to do it...
I have 49 on me.
Okay, 49.
Let's see if it's...
If it goes down over time.
Also, why are you not spawning more babies, huh?
Come on.
Not having enough sex.
Maybe they can't move over there, because it's too tiny of a space.
Let me go to bed.
You guys better have sex while I sleep.
Still 49?
Hmm...
Come on!
What's that sound?
Something just got broken.
I guess I could have two deployers.
And then half it, you know?
Half and half.
24, 25.
Come on, eat!
Eat, eat, eat!
This may be too high for them.
You know?
I think they...
What was that sound again?
Oh, they are...
I think they're eating the floor.
Come on.
Okay, let me check.
Are you full?
No!
Okay, it doesn't work then.
It doesn't work.
Shit.
Oh no.
Give me that.
Stack him and rack him.
Damn.
There needs to be one lower then.
I mean, that's fine.
Except they're gonna escape while I do this, I think.
Huh.
This is getting a little too tight anyway, isn't it?
We could have something that feeds from this side here.
I
need to get in there somehow.
I gotta be quick though, I gotta be quick.
Oh!
Oh no, I'm stuck in here with them.
Aha!
Come on!
God damn it.
Okay, fine.
You get a little bit bigger enclosure, okay?
I get it.
Your union has paid off.
I listen to you.
Come here.
Best I can do.
And then...
I guess we're gonna...
Yes, that's it.
And then...
I need you to come...
Come in here with me.
Come on.
Even further.
Further.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Back here, back here, back here.
Gotcha!
And now, close that off.
You cannot leave.
Now we just have to connect this.
It's gonna be annoying, but...
It is what it is.
Oh.
Like that.
Oh, we don't even need to do that.
We can just shaft it.
Did I get rid of my shafts?
Damn.
Has the spinning been low?
Oh, nice.
It is.
Oh, I have a lot.
Nice.
Fifty-one shafts.
Ah, it would make more sense to put this on the other side, I guess.
I changed my mind.
Let's put it on the other side.
Whew!
That was a fast one.
Now we gotta do this super fast.
I need to get in here.
There we go.
And then, I need you guys to get over here!
Come here, come here!
There, eat.
Get out of the way.
That's it.
Now rotate it the way I want it.
No.
Brother, please.
What is the trick with this?!
I
don't understand!
This is the worst system of all time!
How the fuck does this shit work?!
Why is it every direction except the one I wanted?!
What do I need to do?!
There it is!
We got it, we got it!
Holy shit!
Okay.
Now, from the bottom.
Vertical shaft.
Gearbox, I mean.
Then we vertical again.
Rotate.
Shaft.
Boom!
Oh!
It just damaged them!
I can't feed it for some reason.
What the fuck?
What's wrong now?
Stop poking them!
Oh my god, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Get out of the way, get out of the way!
Get out of the way!
Fucking...
Gimme that!
Wait!
Wait, it's not working now!
What?!
Oh, wait!
Oh!
Please!
Wait, we had it, we had it, we had it!
There it is!
What's wrong now?
I swear to god, these systems are...
Oh...
Did we do it?!
Wait, what?
Am I...
Why doesn't it work?!
Uh...
Oh, wait!
I can't see shit, move out of the way!
This should work!
Wha...
Does it not have a shaft below?!
It does!
So what's the problem?
Wait, the...
Oh, this got turned into a...
Non-vertical?
Or what?
Deployer cannot activate!
It appears this Deployer contains excess items that need to be extracted!
What do you mean?
Is...
Is that not the whole function of it?
To hold items?
Cheap...
Please get out...
Get the fuck out of the way, will ya?
We have so much room to move in!
I...
So, wait, there's...
There's items inside of this right now?!
Okay!
Weird!
Yes!
Feed him!
Come on, please!
You better stay in there!
Yes!
That's what I'm talking about!
Feed him good!
Feed him hard!
Uh...
And then here...
Make it pretty, I guess...
Okay...
And now...
They're having sex, that's wonderful!
Make it a bit smaller...
Did I just get experience?
What happened there?
Wait!
The kids are moving out!
Oh!
There we go!
Okay, now they can't move!
Good, good, good!
No, no, no, no!
It needs to be...
Like this...
No, no, no!
Okay, good!
Uh...
Gantry shaft needs to be a little...
Longer...
Gantry...
Shaft...
Oh!
You need to come back inside!
You can't be out here!
Break!
One sec!
You need to come inside!
Come in!
Come on, little one!
Little one!
You too!
Come on, please!
Yes, yes, yes!
And then...
In!
Little one!
Bluhuhuh!
Jesus!
I'm losing my fucking mind!
Get in!
Yeah!
Boom!
That's how we do it!
We may need to extend the gantry shaft even more!
One more!
Eight!
I can't wait to flip this switch and watch all of you die!
You heard me!
I just need you to have one more child!
Get fed, nerd!
Come on!
Have children!
Maybe...
You know what?
I feed you manually a little bit here!
Okay, you're...
You're fed as hell!
Good!
I like that!
I just need one more child and then we can...
Cheers, guys!
While that is happening, let's get this...
Whatchamacallit...
Let's set up the mechanism for collecting the items!
And all I need for that is a...
Hopper!
Or four of them!
Ah, that's gonna be...
How expensive is it actually?
Okay, five per...
And I have...
Didn't I bring home a lot of iron?
At least from this mining trip?
There's gotta be some.
Great.
A single iron.
Oh well!
I can't believe that only was a single iron.
It's crazy.
I don't even wanna blast this.
Just out of principle.
Oh, would you look at that?
Oh, wait!
We need an output for this!
Whoops!
Otherwise, this is...
Yeah.
Ah, yeah.
Didn't think about that.
But hey, we're getting experience from it.
It's something.
Uh...
So how much iron do I actually have?
So we have one hopper here that I could use.
I guess we're not using it anyway.
Really?
Uh...
No more.
I'm...
Iron starved, man.
Jesus.
I'm gonna go get some iron.
I can't even do it because I don't have a right pickaxe.
Pain!
Unimaginable pain!
Like, I...
Okay, hold on.
Can we find...
I need to think.
There's gotta be a way to just generate iron, man.
Ugh!
Iron.
Nah.
At least not what I know of now.
Uh, let's see if something has happened out here in the meantime.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, no!
Wait, I didn't mean for all of you to grow up all of a sudden.
That's bad.
Oh, my God, dude.
One more child!
Come on!
I need one more!
You can do it!
And...
They're gonna be out of sync now!
Okay, you know what?
Fuck it!
DIE!
Hold on.
I just clicked something I shouldn't have!
Okay, there we go.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
And back we go!
Get squeezed!
Oy!
Look at that!
Fuck you!
It works!
Fantastic!
Very nice.
Now, obviously, I need another sheep now, but that was worth it.
I absolutely needed to see it.
I just had to see it.
I couldn't wait.
Man, oh, man.
Did I even pick up the items?
Now I did.
I got him.
Zombie?
Get him!
Attack!
Come on, attack!
Get him!
Come on, buddy!
You're supposed to protect me!
There we go, thank you.
Sit back down.
Okay.
Fill this up.
Uh, so the plan now...
Is to go get iron.
So...
We are gonna go to a deeper level.
And we're gonna fucking destroy nature.
Don't need all of this.
Chains.
Uh, yeah.
Although, I would say maybe redstone at this point.
Not sure.
I'm ready.
Let's go to a deeper level where there's probably some iron and go crazy.
It's outside.
Alright.
The insane thing is...
Like, it's just...
I feel like it's the chicken and the egg situation in this game constantly.
I need food!
But to make food, like...
And I mean a lot of food...
I need hoppers to collect the food.
And to make hoppers to collect the food, I need iron!
So I gotta go dig!
And I also wanna go dig in the nether.
But for that I need food!
Oh yeah?
Don't care about you.
Let's go further down.
To a...
A really nice level.
Oh, did I...
Okay, good.
I have some torches.
Look at me.
Frickin' uh...
Mowgli.
From Jungle Book.
No, wait.
Tarzan.
From Jungle Book.
I feel like this is not a good spot...
Oh, I do see iron though.
Maybe this is an...
An okay depth.
We can uh...
Yeah.
Why not?
Let's...
Let's dig here.
Just gonna find a good...
Last spot here.
Oh!
What's wrong with my...
Personality?
Let's do it here.
Alright, alright, alright, alright.
Beautiful.
Put it in motion.
That's right, industrialization.
Get used to it, bitch.
Waste products are being ejected.
Lovely.
Show me that iron.
I'm gonna be ready to pick it up as well...
In case...
Shit goes south.
I love this machine.
I love it.
Lovely experience.
That's probably coal.
Wait a minute!
Uh...
Like, okay.
I don't have a train yet.
But with this minecart.
With the furnace inside.
I can link it to another minecart that I sit inside.
And we just go!
Along a track.
No need for powered redstone rails.
Dude, hell yeah.
A temporary mini-train can be made.
Let's see what it's collected so far.
Yay!
Some iron!
Oh shit.
Uh oh!
This machine is not equipped to handle this.
Cover the...
Holes!
Plug them!
Wait, it's...
It's working.
Wait!
Rails...
Uh...
Reject water!
Rails are hydrophobic.
Wait, is it just working?
There's no way!
Shit!
Oh, it's going through water!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, this machine is amazing.
It's even better than I thought!
It's making a bridge and everything!
I mean, I mean, come on!
Wow!
I do want to pluck this though.
This is horrible.
Let's plug it while it's doing its thing back there.
Ah, come on!
Block it!
There we go!
Oh no!
It's one of those...
terrible situations.
I will never get rid of this water!
I got rid of the water!
Incredible.
That was a pain though.
Like...
Oh, it's just going back there.
Industrialization doesn't stop for nobody.
Not even me.
It just goes.
You know, you set it in motion and...
things just develop.
Oh, there's animals in between.
Hey, what's up guys?
They're protesting against the industrialization here.
They don't know that this is progress and they can't stop it.
And all their kicking and screaming is not gonna change anything, you know?
Let's light it up at least so that doesn't happen again.
I'm sure it has found some iron.
Damn!
Dude!
Man!
The amount of iron here is...
sickeningly little.
This is not the way to get iron.
Holy crap, man.
Feels like we're just...
missing the iron all the time.
Like, look at this!
Perfectly cutting through all the areas with no iron.
Like, what the hell?
Also, we may need to fill this up with more, uh...
stuff.
We can keep making bridges.
That was my last torch.
Oh!
That's rails!
We can make rails here.
Or get rails, easily.
Nice.
Oh, I can also make sticks, actually.
More torches.
And I must be getting a lot of coal here, right?
Not... okay, some.
Not that much, but some.
This is getting a little...
questionable.
What happened?
It stopped!
Wait, what just happened?
Wait, what the...
It's like it...
Oh!
That's funky!
It went on the rails that were already here.
Oh, that's messed up.
That is like one in a million.
I can't believe that happened.
Iron!
Nice!
The name tag...
I kinda want those.
Oi!
Infinity!
Not bad!
Hell yeah.
Okay.
We gotta pick this guy up, though.
Oh my god, I can't even destroy that.
Got it.
It's as easy as that!
That's how you pick the whole thing up when something goes south.
It's nice.
Bop bop bop bop bop bop.
And now we just put it back on the track and everything should be...
smooth sailing.
Maybe this thing can...
go away.
How is this harder to destroy than obsidian?
Excuse me?
Unimaginable pain.
Oh.
I will never do that again in my life.
That was a once in a lifetime thing.
Man, it's beautiful.
Why is it so slow?
Oh, did we ran out of...
Ah!
There's no more juice!
I get it.
Oh, now we're going.
Hell yeah.
I love the waste products being expelled on the side.
So neat.
16...
I mean...
Okay.
Hey, we're getting a diorite, though.
We can use that to make andesite.
That's something.
It's not all lost, you know?
It's not...
Hopeless.
Lots of diorite being destroyed here.
I wonder if it's also digging faster with the actual, um...
Drills, because I'm using the powered thing here now.
Maybe the speed of the mechanism or the contraption determines...
How fast, uh...
These things are spinning, you know?
Surprisingly non-eventful, this tunnel.
Not a lot of trouble on the way.
It's nice.
This thing has changed everything, though.
Like, the plow...
Is doing...
Wonders.
I think it's removing gravel there.
Uh-oh.
Let's see how well this goes.
Wait, what is it removing?
Oh, that's awkward.
Wow.
Pain.
Unimaginable pain.
But, hey, it's going.
I could just leave it to its own devices and go off somewhere.
Come back in, like, ten years.
It's on the other side of the world.
I guess it needs more, uh, coal, but yeah.
I do wonder, though.
It's weird that it doesn't automatically grab the coal from the chest.
You know?
Only 17 iron.
After mining thousands and thousands of blocks.
That is so disappointing.
Okay, I've had enough.
Stop.
No more.
Let's go back.
And look, it's like I'm always barely missing all the iron.
It's insane, actually.
How is this possible?
Like, you see all the iron that we found on the way?
Like, in the roof, on the ceiling, on the walls?
We would have had, like, at least double if we had just gotten some of the up and down iron.
Too bad.
Wish I had a proper pickaxe so I could actually take it with me.
Look, this one, too.
Let's try going down to diamond level and see what it will find.
I'm curious.
Let's just go deeper and deeper.
We could even, um...
Make...
Yeah.
We could also just keep making this deeper.
Like, this tunnel, specifically.
That would also be kind of fun.
So, we're doing a 3x3 in height, I think.
So...
No, let's...
No, no.
Let's, um...
I mean, we're gonna end up making a Swiss cheese mountain here.
Does it matter?
I don't think it matters.
I mean, there's a million mountains.
Who cares?
Let's just keep going down.
Go!
Sweet.
Follow me if you dare.
Oh, my.
You survived that, huh?
I've already been here, of course.
Let's go one deeper.
Shit!
Oh, thank...
God!
That was water!
I would've died!
Ooh!
Panic attack!
Wow!
That was also my last steak I just ate.
Wait a minute.
Didn't I write down something related to this?
Didn't I write something about limits and knowing when to...
I guess I didn't, so I guess I don't have to follow that advice.
Let's keep going.
We're gonna dig.
This way.
Right here.
Here.
Are you ready?
We're gonna find all the good stuff now.
Trust.
I mean, nothing's gonna hurt us down here.
We got torches everywhere.
We're gonna make sure the tunnel is lit.
One thing though, what happens if lava comes?
Uh oh.
I guess I just pick it up and go.
Just like the nether.
I pick it up quick and leave.
That's it.
Cover...
Plug in the holes and then keep going.
That's the way.
Oh crap!
Didn't think about that.
Yeah, that's kinda scary.
Let's just light that up.
Oh, I have bread!
Nice!
We do have food.
Perfect.
Are you running out of steam here or...?
Ah, you are.
Good.
What is taking so long to mine?
Oh, it's this crap!
It's always gravel, isn't it?
Gravel is the enemy of progress.
Wait, are we just going along a...
It's not even a hole we're gonna make.
Why is it so slow?
Hold on, I need to see.
Oh, it's taking a long time to mine the sink, it seems.
That's the bottleneck here.
And also, some of these rocks are kinda harder to mine, it seems.
Weird.
Wait, look!
It needs like four attempts to mine it!
That's a buck!
What the hell is that?!
Wait, what?!
Like, actually, what's going on here?
Wait, is it because we're somehow...
Maybe...
Maybe the full box has something to do with it?
Oh wait, don't throw in the...
I feel like this is bugged.
Why is it trying to remine the same thing four times, and failing?
That doesn't make any sense.
And it's not a gravity thing where it falls down, you know?
Okay, now it's going.
I mean, okay.
Now it seems to work.
What are we finding?
You know what, let me change the filter here.
Oh wait, I...
I guess I can't do that in motion.
Oh, I have to...
do it like that.
Now it's pooping it.
What happened?
Wait.
I mean, I don't know why I just stopped.
Okay, here we go, here we go, here we go.
We're back in business.
DIAMOND!
I'll definitely mine that, even with this pickaxe.
We just unlocked a bunch of shit.
Take some gold.
I feel like most of what is being caught here is crap.
But, I mean, it is a nice way to make a tunnel.
That is pretty much confirmed, right?
And, check it out.
Maybe sometimes when we reach tough, we'll find one of those large areas with a lot of iron.
And when we find that, we can start digging manually.
For example, right there, you see there's iron on tough?
This could be one of those.
17 iron right now, let's see.
Before we go to the nether, we're gonna increase the size of this machine to make it even bigger.
Because the drills are not that hard to make now.
We have some iron now, we can make more drills.
It's gonna go insane-o-style.
Okay, we're getting some redstone now.
Actually, diorite we keep.
I like that.
Anticite as well, oops.
Getting a little bit of everything.
Ha ha ha, sick!
That sounds nice.
Look at this.
It stopped.
Why?
Why hast thou stopped?
Did you run out of...
Oh!
Oh, interesting.
Oh no!
Shit.
There we go.
We may have to just temporarily do that.
How am I gonna...
Get it going.
There we go.
There we go, there we go, there we go.
Oh.
Oh, it's gonna make a crazy bridge!
This is a little dangerous.
Hey, I've been here too, look at that!
Wow.
Is that diamond?
No, that's sink.
Shit.
This is scary!
This is actually pretty scary.
Oh.
Is it...
Is it killing animals?
Please let it be.
Oh!
That can happen?
Oh no, don't tell me it hit the lava.
Oh no.
Fuck!
Well, that's the end of that machine.
We just lost I don't know how many drills.
The digging has to be temporarily halted.
Oh my god.
And we only got 17 iron out of this whole fucking expedition.
That is...
Crazy work.
What a disaster, man.
I can't even bring it back home now.
Can I?
No, I can't.
That's...
That's just...
depressing.
You don't need this.
Or this.
Uh...
Man.
Get rid of tough.
I'm taking only the most pressing things.
Like andesite.
And some of this stuff.
Blue stuff.
Rails, of course.
That's it.
I shall leave the rest here for now.
Go away that.
Give me this thing.
We'll have to make this from scratch.
That's no problem.
Go back.
Dude, I haven't eaten anything today other than breakfast.
I'm just now feeling it.
It's hitting me.
I gotta eat.
The question is, where did I even ascend?
Or...
Oh, I guess right here.
Oh, it wasn't even that long of a tunnel.
Nice.
Get up.
Oh, I even made three torches here.
Signifying this is the way up, pal.
Beautiful.
We even have a bridge ready and everything.
Past me thought of everything.
Oh, I...
I wish I got at least one more diamond so I could have made a new pickaxe.
Don't even have that.
Oops, I think it's over here.
This is a very bad path.
I think I...
...have better options.
Yeah, like this one.
And there's my...
...lovely staircase.
The water power that's...
...powering my little factory over here.
Making tuff tuff sounds.
Satisfying.
But the real thing is, like, uh...
We got some diamond now.
I mean, uh...
Iron.
So we can make, I think, the amount we need in terms of...
...hoppers.
Which means we're gonna fix our food situation.
Hopefully for good.
Deposit everything.
Let's cook this iron.
We're gonna cook this as well, of course.
And let's see how much we have.
So with 17 iron and...
Oh, we have 64 iron nuggets.
Sick.
This could be it then.
12 already?
Okay.
And hopper...
...needs 5 each.
And chests as well.
Okay, that's 4.
Plus 1 we have.
That's 5.
Uh...
Where is that hopper, anyway?
There it is.
We're gonna have exactly enough for 6.
Which I think is the perfect amount!
Ah, wait.
We need one more then.
Damn.
Too bad.
Don't have a little iron.
Oh, we have this one!
Sick.
We have just the right amount now.
And then we also need one extra chest.
Because things need to come out somewhere, right?
Hopper.
There we go.
7 hoppers and a chest.
The floor is hopper.
That's the game we're gonna play.
1, 2, 3...
Oh yeah, we need another sheep.
Fuck.
Uh...
I'll worry about that in a second here.
I'm digging with my hands.
Even though...
No, I have a shovel, guys.
So...
What we're gonna do is this.
We're gonna do...
That way.
And...
I'm gonna go in from this side.
Oops!
There we go.
There.
Nice.
That may even be enough.
Like...
I think items that fall there are gonna fall in here too.
Maybe...
Let's do one more just to be absolutely safe.
Like that.
And this one leads that way.
Uh...
Actually, let's not be...
Let's just save a little bit here.
Like that.
It's kinda scuffed, but you know, it should work.
We're gonna put this on a daylight timer or something.
And we have to make sure that we don't kill...
Too much at once.
So we...
So...
Maybe every two days or something.
Just to make sure, you know?
This thing seems like it has already used up all the wheat.
So we gotta connect...
The wheat up here with that down there as well.
To make it self-sustaining.
So let's go find some cow.
I mean sheep.
Or some cows as well.
I mean both.
Are pretty good.
And this time I'm gonna bring a lead if I can make one.
Lead...
Do I have some already?
No, but we need this.
Uh...
Didn't I bring home like a shit ton of string?
Not too long ago?
Come on, don't be like that.
I got no string?
That's wild, man.
Alright.
Way to kill my dreams.
Wow.
Fine.
I'll do it the old-fashioned way.
I don't need more than...
Some wheat anyway.
So I know there's sheep back there.
Oh!
Oh yes!
There we go!
Come here, buddy!
That is so wonderful.
What I got for you.
Now it's gonna be a problem to get this guy inside the enclosure.
It's gonna be another pain point, isn't it?
My...
My life is gonna be ruined for the next...
Three minutes.
Yeah, how am I even gonna do this?
Like...
Crazy.
I guess we do it in stages.
Hmm...
Follow me.
Alright, stay there.
That's fine too.
I need a fence.
More than that.
Oh, come here.
So in stages...
Oh, sorry.
Come here.
I'm sorry!
Come on!
You see, I have it.
There we go.
Come inside.
Oh, that's beautiful!
Yeah!
That was easy!
Oh my god!
Wow!
That was the most smooth thing I've ever done.
Incredible.
In fact, we don't even need these two right here.
I just realized.
That's overkill.
We're gonna save some hoppers.
The only problem is, we just gotta reorient some of these then.
Uh...
This one's gonna...
Point in that direction.
And this one...
In... that one.
Hopefully, the other ones are pointing as they should.
That one's pointing that way.
That's good.
I think we have done it!
This should be good!
Alright, come here.
The machine shall feed you.
Except, wait a minute, why is the machine still?
It's not moving.
Oh, right.
I removed the crucial components.
Wait, what?
Okay, there we go.
It's working.
Now please get out of the way so I can...
Aim!
Get fed.
That's one.
Now, don't look at me.
Don't look at me.
Now, obviously...
Hmm...
It would be better if I had two of them to feed at the same time.
Because there is a bit of delay, because this guy is not even fed yet.
And they're gonna have to sort of...
There we go!
And now, a baby is born.
Alright.
So that's the first step.
Everything that falls out here is gonna go into the chest.
Which is great.
Now, when the killing starts...
This is the thing, right?
There is a possibility that whenever the kill mechanism is activated, that we are not gonna be left with any more...
Adults that can make children.
So, we have to somehow make sure that every time we activate this mechanism that there's at least two children.
If not more.
And that's the thing I'm not quite understanding how to do.
Uh...
I mean, okay, wait.
There's actually not that much room.
I wonder what happened...
Remember that one time in the other Minecraft world I had?
In Season 2.
I had this chicken pen.
With like a million chickens.
At some point, they just started dying.
Because there wasn't any more space.
And they actually got squished against the sides, I guess.
Similar to how...
This thing is squishing that way.
So maybe...
If I just feed them.
Over time.
And they start to overcrowd this place.
And they start to squish each other into the walls.
Wait, isn't that just...
Exactly what I need?
Unless that's also killing off children.
Hmm...
So basically...
Wait a minute actually.
That's...
That is much simpler.
If it works.
Let's just...
Leave it.
In fact, what I'm gonna do...
I'm gonna take a break now.
And uh...
Well, break.
I'm gonna stop.
I'm gonna go eat food.
Because I'm literally starving.
And I'm gonna let this run.
While I eat.
After the stream is done.
For like...
Maybe half an hour to an hour.
And I'm gonna just exit the world after that.
And come back next time.
And see what happens.
So that...
That's what we're gonna do.
This is like the test.
You know?
But now I'm gonna pause though.
And I'm gonna reactivate when it's time.
We're gonna stop there.
Ethical farming.
Uh...
Not really.
You know?
But I mean...
It is what it is.
I gotta do what I gotta do.
Is to get my meat.
At this point, it's getting a little ridiculous.
The amount of times I just...
Have problems with my food supply.
What if you just left the stream running for hours on end.
As we watch the sheep proliferate and die.
I could...
I guess I could...
Leave it running for a bit.
But...
People are gonna be confused by it.
You know?
Like, where is he?
What's happening?
Why is he live?
I think it's confusing.
Why doesn't he talk to chat?
I'm here!
I'm talking to you right now!
Usually when I play, I'm so absorbed by the game.
I don't really...
Look at chat at all.
I don't talk to chat during gameplay.
When I play, I just wanna play.
You know?
Some games though, I do talk to chat while I play.
Depends on the game.
The confusion is the personality of the channel.
Is it?
Is that how you see the channel?
Is this channel confusing?
Maybe a bit.
There's a lot of live streams that are very much confusing.
You're correct.
Like, there's people who are just sleeping on stream.
And there's like thousands of people watching that.
Like...
How is that even happening?
Like, how do you get to that point?
It's crazy.
What are you gonna eat?
I don't know.
What am I gonna eat?
Uh...
I'll probably eat something very boring.
Like...
Rye bread with some stuff on it.
I think right now I have some...
Um...
Uh...
Garnish, I guess.
With some vegetables in it.
And some spices.
It's...
Rolled sausage?
Yeah, I guess.
Exactly.
Yep.
I did have steak and frites yesterday.
And it was amazing.
I'm gonna have it today as well.
Because I have some left.
In fact, I, uh...
I bought...
Um...
What is it called?
Sweet potato fries.
And I made those instead.
And it was actually incredible.
Actually, my headache went away!
I had it a little bit earlier, but now it's gone.
So that's nice.
I can't catch the streams anymore since you're streaming earlier.
This was just today.
I'm gonna stream at all kinds of different times.
Sometimes later, sometimes normal time.
It's gonna be a little all over the place.
I will slowly turn all the live watchers into partial...
VOD watcher covenant people.
Some people loved it because it's earlier than usual.
And usually they can't catch my streams because they're too late for them, you know?
No more 15 schedules?
Nah, most streams will be around 15.
Think of it like a normal distribution.
You know, where the top, the peak...
The median or the mean is gonna be 15.
And then, you know...
There's a chance it'll be much earlier, but it's like a very low chance.
And there's also a chance that it'll be later, but...
Low chance, you know?
You're starting to get very comfortable with Create's principles.
It's very cool to watch.
It's definitely getting better.
But I do find myself with moments where I'm just utterly overwhelmed by all the concepts and all the different blocks that are at my disposal.
A lot of the times when I have an issue and I need to solve something...
I think to myself, okay, there is a way to do it.
I know there is.
But there's like so many different possible ways that I can probably do it.
And I immediately think of the best way to do it.
Like, I wanna find the best way to do it.
And that stops my...
That's like a blocker to my progress, I think.
Because I scour through the pages to try and find the most optimal thing immediately, which is not what I need to do.
Yeah, it is a big toolbox.
Can you imagine how it would have been if I had access to all of that from the start?
I would... I probably wouldn't even have gotten this far at all.
I would have maybe quit.
But this gradual, you know, unlocking of the components makes it bearable.
Yeah, I would die in real life.
I would... just die of a stroke.
There's still a couple things in there, and I look at it and go, okay, but what's the point?
Yeah, I feel that way too.
Like, the turntable.
Okay, but what's the point, you know?
Maybe the point is to put a cake on it and have it spin.
Why?
Just because.
A spinning cake, you know?
It's cool.
What time is in Denmark?
It's 15.53.
The 3rd of September.
2026.
Did the turntable get used today?
It did not.
I think I tried it once.
Maybe on the very first world before I deleted it and made the second world.
My experience of playing Create is also of not knowing what to do first, even not streaming.
Yeah.
Are you just making up stuff as you go as well?
Trying to...
Basically, I'm playing Minecraft normally.
Like, I'm doing the normal progression of Minecraft, just with Create added in, you know?
Like, okay, I gotta get food, but now I have access to all these Create things.
That allow me to potentially make food easier to get, you know?
Or, in this case, a drilling machine.
So, it's like Minecraft plus, in a way, for me.
It didn't drastically change how I play the game.
It's just like an added layer on top.
Turntables are for mechanically induced vomit.
Yeah, I can imagine.
The other day, I was dancing in front of Jackie.
Just to mess with her, you know?
Sometimes I do that.
I make sounds and I dance.
To make her think like, what the fuck is going on?
And I was spinning.
And I was like, holy shit, I'm too old.
I can't spin anymore.
I get sick.
Hahaha.
Man.
Spinning really makes you sick.
At least, it does me.
You need to shift your block brain to gear brain.
For sure, man.
I agree.
Ever gonna put the elytra on a pig?
Hahaha.
Maybe.
Didn't even know you could do that.
I don't think you can do that.
I think you're messing with me.
Would you add more mods this season?
Maybe a food mod?
Maybe.
Probably not.
This was a nice, different stream though.
It felt kinda different, you know?
Streaming in the morning and then into the midday.
So for those that don't know, I started the stream with Deadlock actually.
While I was drinking my coffee and I'd just woken up, you know?
Some games with that.
Some nice games.
And after that we jumped into Minecraft for a while.
And that was kinda nice.
Maybe I'll have more of those types of dual streams where I do one game into another.
We'll see how it goes.
And yes, I will wear wigs.
It'll happen in approximately two weeks.
The date has been set.
Get your snacks.
Prepare yourself.
Wigs will happen.
I'm homesick the last two days, so your timing works for me.
Perfect.
Every time I read your name, Cheezmoo, I think of cheesecake.
And I love cheesecake so much and I haven't been able to find any anywhere.
It's not a very popular thing in Denmark.
At least not something you can buy in the supermarkets.
And I want it!
Make some...
I don't have the skills!
I don't know how to make cheesecake.
The best part of cheesecake for me is the bottom.
I like the...
The cracker bottom, you know?
Or the...
The one made of...
What's it called?
Is it crackers?
It's just so good, man.
The crumbly...
Uh...
Yeah, graham crackers or...
Digestive...
Yeah, digestive crackers.
Exactly, that's the one, you know?
You squeeze them into little pieces and you make the bottom of it.
Oh my god, it's amazing.
Just get a springform pan.
Dude, that's like you saying...
Here, draw a couple lines and then draw the rest of the fucking bird.
I feel like it's...
Maybe it's easier than it seems, but...
It always seems like such a hard thing.
Baking, you know?
Do you want me to explain why the mining machine failed to break some blocks sometimes?
Yeah, okay.
Tell me it...
Tell me it's not...
A bug.
Is it a bug?
Yes or no?
That's all I need to know.
It's...
It's not a bug?
Bro.
If it's not a bug, then...
Okay.
Alright.
I just don't see how it's not.
Like, that...
Looked broken to me.
You haven't had a single create bug so far?
Oh yeah?
But I've definitely created bugs.
Actually, I haven't.
I have had...
I had a bug today!
Remember on my hotbar?
There was an invisible item.
It...
The...
The deployer disappeared.
Boom!
Practically unplayable.
You saw it, I saw it.
That's not create?
Oh shit.
Oh well.
Haha!
But that was a bug.
If you were about to tell me that was a feature, I would have screamed.
Okay.
It's a classic Minecraft bug.
Got it.
It seems to be happening when you very quickly right click.
You know?
It's almost like you're putting something in a spot where it can't go in between game ticks, if you know what I mean.
You know how every game runs on a timer?
Or on a loop?
It's probably something related to that where if you go too fast, and you do something in between those timer clicks, something bad happens.
You know?
Basically, desync between client and server parts of the program.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, so I heard that Minecraft always sort of runs on a server, even locally.
So that's probably that.
Makes sense.
Isn't that also how most duplication bugs in most games happen?
You know, you have a server that has one information, and you have a client that has different information.
And when you mess with that, you can, you know, convince the server that you had more than you were supposed to or something.
I think that's how that usually works, or how people exploit that.
I don't know when the next Minecraft stream is.
But I would maybe say in two days.
Day after tomorrow.
Loosely.
So you hacked Minecraft?
Oh yeah, I hacked everything about it.
It is so hacked.
I can't wait for nether drilling either, Chismu.
The thing is though, I want to be ready this time.
Like, no mistakes.
I need a full inventory of food and meat.
You know, I need to be ultra ready.
I want to have the biggest machine ever.
I need to frickin' destroy the nether.
What next game after DDLC?
Maybe...
DDR.
I tried to think of other games that had that acronym, but I don't think there's anything close.
No, it'll probably be something very different from, you know, visual novels type deal.
I just want something completely different.
Something with a lot of gameplay.
I don't know what.
I don't know what TS2 is.
Dishonored feels like a game that would be better played offline.
It sounds like that's a story game, right?
What will you call the drill?
It's gonna be named Bill.
Of course.
I'm still thinking about it.
Maybe I'll let you guys decide on the next stream game.
I'll make a little poll or something.
Maybe a puzzle game, actually.
Could be.
Maybe a scary game.
Dude, a scary game for stream.
I've never done that.
I don't think, at least.
Maybe that's gonna be a thing we do.
Honestly, I'm in the mood for a lot of things right now.
Could be scary, puzzle...
I'm also thinking something like Hitman, you know?
Like gameplay-heavy games.
Because that's like a stealth game.
And that could be fun.
Okay.
I'm gonna go, guys.
Thank you for watching.
This was a cool stream.
Nice to try something a little different at a different time.
I wish you a wonderful day.
And tomorrow's Friday, so...
Get ready.
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye!